<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oot 'n' a'scoot</title>
    <description>The adventures of Valkyrie and Evan Savage Vespa-ing across America.
</description>
    <link>http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 19:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 19:23:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>thend</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;What felt endless so&lt;br /&gt;
Short a time ago, now draws&lt;br /&gt;
To a final close.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Waking up not so very bright nor so very early, we rolled out of the hotel at about 9am. It was a hard thing to make ourselves shimmy back into our still-soaked jeans, although at least our jackets and shirts had dried out and we had fresh underwear and socks to apply. The wind on the bike evaporated water off our clothes, chilling our legs and nether regions into sadness. We promised ourselves a decent breakfast, but the only “restaurant” we saw on our route was a Tim Horton’s. We stopped and got bagels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/AHwbSFgeNDHqVAxGy73QH2XQJFRXDduQTnprqF7kQK_N0X1cvbffYpxuQnj6eZxxPSFMiV8ry0lX_dFyEv2qDMrkPLRtzwcHAFkEak4-2n8h7nr694HXA6u3CH8opYxf16f9Wuww99S6dCiDxu24uAyR4pYvc6W722iaEyWjNwaH8_FUVm8zHb-E0iAYQ9P4PKe7ESmA-blu-0QBYx2aCT9DzuoRTl6iVdNNXrU6ihh4tVUZFUWFVYdgPJNcSp-KCGwGobQerIfelLUiJKGtTRve1DqVo4jmmbqOiRKuU6dL9367mTO9tXjxtauQ5V1792sTHfma1hTI-TXicqyMxDQsbo90DHZK2cmFde97SsTbJIqz77RoB70W7-QgM9gyQtETG0RtgW7QeMgKWvkLRwV2HdATJ4wZ4dZF4CODqVTGjTJoVPKBPSofQeATd9BLTq4lyy3Gm0jYG36d9Sx76fXdO9LYqGRvju9MDcy9hoQm48Z6OJZW3so2sWkIOXw9zSt0-OuYLyH-eGu8sUcRb2fkAi7iFAnpKgrtnM95n500TQnXiEl1KiwQjzr2hxz7F8kq1GAwimHsLCyfW10lH7QQZUU5lZA-R7IJu8gcC1j8gya_=w804-h1420-no&quot; alt=&quot;Flag&quot; title=&quot;Flag&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we sat there, we reminisced about the trip that was somehow already coming to an end. Yesterday was hard, by far the coldest and wettest day we’ve ridden, but the overall trip is filled with warm feelings and happy memories. It’s hard to believe today was our last day. As we gave in to nostalgia, we got one last chance to enjoy the incredulous looks people give the Emperor in his decked out state. One fellow walking by in the parking lot turned around no less than four times as he walked by, as though unconvinced he’d seen properly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall ride today was short and rather pleasant: though the clouds threatened to open on us again, they didn’t, and we made Niagara-on-the-Lake in about an hour via the lakeshore. Just across the lake, we can already see the city where we’ll be, soon enough, living.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evan’s mom welcomed us as we arrived, and spent a non-negligible amount of time fawning over our scooter and how funny it looked. She very kindly cooked us some breakfast as we loaded our soaked and stinking things into the laundry machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And here we are. The end! We’ve just go to figure out what to do now…!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 15:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/30/thend.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/30/thend.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Any Port in a Storm</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-37-waterloo-on-to-grimsby-on&quot;&gt;Day 37: Waterloo, ON to Grimsby, ON&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today was originally going to take us down to Lake Erie, but instead takes us through persistent and dreary rain to a hotel off the water near Grimsby.  Not exactly the most triumphant penultimate day, but sometimes you take what you can get…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/3Rg2NMqd4wPjBq9H7lIyE969ZYlWAFWUh7tY5mEDTF8SJbhXsU9an2LtreNp6jB7XrAe5XulsDDYRI8WztRoq2MQGrR36B633N8tOv2reyc388WRmx2xUNKUuAq2E8p1QfBqiMg-2E8buFDqhLf37X6wd7J97Hm2fcAPjiR9UsLmWD4txGtRVY3ctwIQ_F9jH7HxLwdAx834EEq7rUzd9oyZSVwSBZVHAZyB8EMjJJuFsshkbpywEdwMyhqlsGbbD0RUvnaYsj3swRvcKC4w2Q4NhJ9gKyRNhjCgJdDDXkHZVPz86Sec_dATTyHxmXajJxWAcmskEH56afuyyclyy3nNoabX8OV-uoifnKF8CXjC7aoG6K6NKYK-nEuoIiustiv9umazrjtPYGg2RqpGIVAM2fc-E3U6J8597bPGeMQbeqR2gbNLcQSb05pzU6pDh4fw8MGtwYyfNtArH9BXdvD0lOuqv1DRjR94EAPSxCoXTherv9YV9rv0dolACQ9vmBu4byF07yGTnrMHohvWHStwfwpfluKQFfVNVtkUv_1ghklt7lFiqmh1YBbL58tJZhk12ylcxGy81lNXO3gDhCUgesc0d3iXAT98X1AoXPOG=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(That photo isn’t actually of today, sadly - we were too wet to even think about taking pictures.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The morning is rainy, and our host Jeff has already headed out to teach his morning yoga class.  We’re exhausted from the long ride yesterday, which was quite possibly the longest of our trip.  The road takes a lot out of even the most travel-hardened of people: the elements, the bouncing and jostling, the constant attention needed to the other vehicles and to the roadside forests from which, at any moment, a trip-ending deer could spring foolishly into your path.  Motorcycle travel is, without a doubt, more tiring than car travel, and though it is not so tiring as hiking or cycling, neither do you get the benefit of exercise that those human-powered forms of transportation bring…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We share a sizeable breakfast of eggs, vegan sausage, and delicata squash with Ben, one of our host’s roommates before poking around downtown Waterloo.  The city has changed considerably since Evan went to university here, the most notable difference being the construction of a light rail line connecting Waterloo, Kitchener, and Cambridge.  This will undoubtedly be a great boon to the area when completed, but in the meantime pedestrian and vehicle traffic alike is mired in a confusing mess of road closures, detours, and temporary one-way restrictions.  The Huether is still there; Lion’s Head has reinvented itself as an upscale craft brewery; the Ukrainian church still sells pierogis; the park has way more historical signage; the Perimeter Institute has some kind of addition along with a new eastern façade.  Plus ça change, plus c’est la même…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rain lets up slightly around noon, and the weather calls for rain right through the weekend, so we reluctantly make the call to leave: we’re so close to the end of the trip, and we feel a personal obligation to finish it!  As we go to load up the bike, we run into an older woman by the name of Theresa, who just can’t believe that we would ride across the country - and in this rain! - on our scooter.  She’s lived in Waterloo for over 30 years, and has probably seen all kinds of changes in that time.  She offers a room in her house as a refuge from the rain, but we’re committed now, and true to character we’re stubborn enough to believe that we just &lt;em&gt;have&lt;/em&gt; to follow through with our ride.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stop in Kitchener for a two-part lunch.  One part is a stop at City Café Bakery’s original Victoria St. location, the other a visit to the farmers’ market building for a stuffed pepper and some pierogis.  Yum!  Except that, by the time we intrepid travellers have finished our meal, the rain is coming down significantly harder.  On towards Cambridge, it beats harder still, then lightens up just in time to meet the other end of the light rail construction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time we crawl through Cambridge downtown, we’re getting quite soaked and have to make a difficult call: do we forge onwards down to Lake Erie, or do we head instead for Lake Ontario and attempt to make it to Niagara-on-the-Lake today?  We decide on the latter, for although we had been very excited about the prospect of one more night camping off the lakes, we have no wish to spend an extra few hours riding through this sort of rain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Along Highway 8, the rain slowly picks up again, so that we’re well and truly drenched as we pass through Dundas and enter into Hamilton.  It’s getting later, and as we pass through the main part of Hamilton we realize we probably won’t make it to Niagara-on-the-Lake after all: in another hour or so, it will be too cold to ride safely.  We persevere long enough to find a hotel off the water near Grimsby, where the receptionist is nice enough to knock $10 off the room rate (because, you know, of &lt;em&gt;course&lt;/em&gt; we have one of those CAA memberships or whatever, right?  &lt;em&gt;wink&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We throw ourselves out of our soggy clothing and directly into a luke-warm shower, where we spend the next 20 minutes gradually restoring warmth to our bodies.  Hypothermia is no joke, and we’re dangerously close to it, but after the shower we feel once more close to human.  Just “human” isn’t enough, though: why not cap off the trip with a fancy dinner in the 8th floor restaurant?  Good question, and we can’t come up with a reason not to, so soon we’re sipping Shiraz and chowing down on truffle parmesan frites as we look out into the storms over Lake Ontario.  Toronto is somewhere out there, but we can’t quite see it - ah well, better eat more maple-bourbon-glazed salmon and medium-rare tenderloin in a &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; tasty red wine-based sauce.  We cap it all off with a visit to the hot tubs before our last night of sleep on this trip, for tomorrow we reach my parents’ house, where we’ll hang up our jackets before heading onwards to Toronto after the weekend…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/29/any-port-in-a-storm.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/29/any-port-in-a-storm.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What in Blue Blazes??</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Farms give way to parks&lt;br /&gt;
The sky shrinks, the vistas close&lt;br /&gt;
Enter the cities.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Awakening in Tobermory, we scraped all our things back into their bags and loaded the bike, then sat down to enjoy a delightful breakfast cooked by a women who was obviously the mother of the man who checked us in yesterday, including fresh homemade spanakopita and bread. A quick stop at the grocery store netted us some snacks for the hike we’ve planned today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We confusedly drove around Tobermory for a few minutes, then finally managed to find our way out to the Bruce Peninsula National Park/Fathom Five National Park Visitors’ Centre (notice the “re” on that, ha!). It was not the only time we’d be lost today. In any case, we paid up for some passes and hopped on the Burnt Point Trail, a side trail of the Bruce (the giant 900km trail that runs all down the Niagara Escarpment from the tip of the Bruce Peninsula to Niagara Falls).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/XK3cYJtwRNRGbiSlQICoZMciUm_zyHzOZBzD0eX_wcC_NMt5-L9WyBIcGvyvDA88GhF2jGLJleDeQcqFDVUHcIMSUjCHJHorLNl6tf-VFwG5OYshxoncwZA9NRWKUsezkzOtNbb_HSDUs4JjQAVOcFXC0mJhZ_zb9V17g16Oud5cmkH7PhYddRDX3oOhFkpuNtp0anhy832kMWTozDre5v3uyWwDjDBCUDCAx9bxdSD_iftiC5YzC4Q7805eQn9VIThd_AYIOV3KPs2QaLWY7EpxqU5z23Dc8-5Sat1eDx6dmtW6CK0J8o2laWcbSG3tHnIR5wr48yVWSKrn4sPAS35LlOL86CqrR60Gx_gHsfjTNghp6jndDSNWWWWOh2pjuFaTJayBYpu3j17rynMtwVhAlYIS834tLzELNGslf8upNwxNvN8bNGc6ZACY-AafbMBkhLfpG0ZLX1nfsKIFuf9Q8szaMiVQhU2Cil3K2qDlNv8KCaAsOFs96FiN8BIw29TuBbX0RRcxc_9fBfqbOTp4AO_Cis6KL-yTi0ZymXvonTN8vAzTUDrYP8GHjVUaYf_uHD8sGkNpdGA5_eVGjyBh2hlbsE_dq4Z0H_7WFTCDLhDfLA=w2480-h1404-no&quot; alt=&quot;Blue Blazes&quot; title=&quot;Blue Blazes&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bruce is demarcated by blazes painted onto trees. A single blaze means go straight. A pair of blazes indicates a turn, in the direction of the one that is higher than the other. White blazes indicate the main Bruce Trail, while blue ones denote side trails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/m0wLb-orVzluc_aqsiYaKp-FUQS4ytK9aoqIbe1v6nTi5SYS52hOhgVPyK68Nba8hWjiiGf0Ep2mKelylQX_fNF5nD2F2imaRoFnQ7uWitjHE5-gOy12sC0tSAAFqV-hdknzNruDiJBr3fLkqMC9r_jAKm2vEq-7JV4qXJdQIKO2mZGz7D2TkYH12ofHtUckLevjWvOc99fy0zT7PEvw9H0aSq-YnLChYRtmEhpyCGKoyeUOS9s2M0W-a_2tWOZc0s88hGgEVKlgFhm6UGt1Sl50zhSDvSPCc8OTpIACLbzSKjh9dA55PM63gbUgPT2_p2e0s5wNEzpufHa19wQ9I8oMqVEhrCFgACCPI8p-B1q_yNRxDNUoe3w9pOtzBNRDbhiz6rJ-i18cTIqP1y5BqU-M24C879AM51vP8mn970pWz5VwAGgrxjnLlk05VTHDIrlInf5lwnDRf757ct_9H4nYBw76atppfpqbnIqG_G1CSCbnyQH_aAlWSANuq3JPn2eSwBhSvvM9UMrPqI8joMGkKDViPXcP2cI7ev1FRLGRAzK1BqXs1wjjRwAUDlcdsK3jW1jgpmTJEpP9fdvjfgHYsDGJ85V5qh08n8CmqTgKXt75EA=w2480-h1404-no&quot; alt=&quot;Georgian Bay&quot; title=&quot;Georgian Bay&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hike was lovely, bringing us through a couple different types of forest and out to the rocky coast. We saw several amazing vistas, as well as some excellent places for relaxing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/H9f5oltb42_N-9eb4y7cyXp7WHkUZZV_Q24fCwCMO-8H4qukTlU4zgmp-17Fb03k0tid3YY_WK41X1HMmxGgpToxFoQxkWD6xWmebMaFnHyhVI1vAcLv5eldxnGsfcxCaziRPMCB0ksooil5A3CA85GxUz-ewQvcLkOUUEG1HZ16U-lBV6HYtqPtX8V994Uvi89NV4V33IbzmsHcbbSASQM2bMRLkDhe6DyTN--7irdoNSuVD1ntZaCIXI2mOop3ctTENuOuSeXjMrUf5RK7o6fI9RESRaLnK8Y_eNLL01ekFybdV2hHxyDHm53Dy1RgzmFs5K-kfhpOMJOF8Hj5TfHSfHeB3xeXRXq3bp0wxRJnL1I9mBUFOEGNhfO8eiX1hvei28wgApYeOxEeuxFqvz3MtsHD_getIWiC-rOzbnyjU2S1e4zMybGl5UNVINWWOmetwdc1munolnqc0D77fy6BO9VGo4-rC7KLi0PiCF0uJ5Mfo07jSplD5yK9snmf5ccdm--dhfQcNnkhvzedYW0CRMD3K5Eat3DGd93J6ikf9Ioo2btMBu74rLFxMGzs29S0xeovpcb-5XO6KFyrHlarHJfkDosip2nhZYbeyzRkPi-tZw=w2480-h1404-no&quot; alt=&quot;Deck Chairs&quot; title=&quot;Deck Chairs&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Nh_XSm3O3i9PE948UnvtiXCc0WNcDW9n5f8tsrhQ4RxVsysWI83PCake9e4AAj8amPuWuM8LP6VGc6GYC-GgDEtEbuC1PbZCW_QPuk4ndZmovx5f3VDFLwtfN3iA6TqUdCZW50ZgZo5GTQzoFCtIZslk4YDAfUxJ58aPOT5_ETNvuwQ8ooXC0fEFOn7bupzUJ3pQpY-Ato2qORZkebjpleT3aY7iqFbJFjgVo6-2VNr3BQ8FtZ5u64ILyFRoGM_Z_411M8AwAQvWLqU4SQ2QgKVUGYTjBwE1bmyKldTJ5GE3BK_ymNRhGTzpk3VlIAPUGQ2sOXiFYLul0_xjbn3Do9xNB5esAth__eEYokCYCFOTn3XD0OSuANJftPnzU1aSlTfsWNhIIg0ZT9_a4Gy9PJBmt9ZgRYdqldeq53LHj_GT2v8-qRYvBiEruPfQMJWWrEqcp5nN0w0NCqO8faQbK0uyzAFBM0dQy-m4DEh5E10A8ycHqn4DjvIopVV17z59dxvepdhayjAPijG1qWN3c5uWNTjdmr0ahifHNQG-ZL1DeXhDsW-qLuE6RqzU76wfgyPnQxclAdXk9xpYQqIfR9Hnh5xQbPfrpKkrpy_d5EdDgs-5Xw=w2480-h1404-no&quot; alt=&quot;Beaver Logo&quot; title=&quot;Beaver Logo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the hike, we climbed up the lookout tower to admire the view, then swung back to the centre where we watched a video (which is copyrighted, hello, “Her Majesty the Queen in Right of Canada”; what happens if Canada ever declares independence? Will the Queen retain copyright over its National Park videos??) about the park, which was extremely Canadian. It followed a park ranger as he explored all the different things around, like the shores, the trees, the caves, and the shipwrecks under the lake. It was actually pretty informative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also tromped around the exhibits in the centre, which we spent some time giggling at. There was an exhibit describing the area’s “ecosystem stew”, and how many different ingredients were required to make something that worked well. There was also one showing underwater footage of shipwrecks and the like that had 3D elements. Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/n8biEIuCcnHXmwdDphhhobUBqhcI9L7W6yM4Pf_1Bfsjktmbmz1ZwRtqyRrtNAoKdGRVbCQrGh9DB3Rcddka-j7ZQ0qeTEfOKP7i8CYMoEvM7XzkwrAVF0pkGkEpQFXmTcFWBd7Tbrp7p968B8onkd2ewnmrq9vDXIm62b1SqEVVNCmtr7sB5Par7ABhHUljN2QlkiNg1_8N8vEl3mTzbSXQIcXyI-CWARyGSHJ6gsljCW_x-0FyVN9k8dnglWtBNd3aggoqW7PKwsKGbzlRoUB_eRtmVMVCHXdkfJGaapnymzX8lwz4b1M7H06F8WjeUGea6fPNd8z8ir9NcwOqh3HhbL1oL0Ect-yQgkNt6b2kQOgWEv-iQsf99IGBfFh4F4ShYsz4ggm_hSJZ9qiWWnGETmLBVExWjK_GKScXFg0FMCzIsXhKnrYZWqVjuselnEkLWNE84U0p1f66ViyCJkmK2w1vwzLo6q4tjqDTRGeGZFFPMwyu4IAbsebLNDF69AgmD20wqHTyH-QErw8O4Xj4FlbwZ9r2CyPTazjIEGVw340jyTm57erW5sXG4i2ULYpAfFWLwL542J9GvckEmL7bSGBVEdyV7b95cVPRqhamp5-kgA=w804-h1420-no&quot; alt=&quot;Ecosystem Stew&quot; title=&quot;Ecosystem Stew&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/sPi7oSxHTYuwakSF3Rx5Bs_vN3RJZs_ir-rAOut5cYb0UckDKrPIO7BBCCkadOPNNUu6DhURwNxLXuFSwIPBIBxVRs5NECfIsdAyjHFBTR2DX0VoHVD3qEQs8Ea786JIt3b6qlOxe09MYmitkHZ26Bxe-iJJI3ikiHefstVKP-R_fCeJadnvAxKz6Uqv9FbufN_26xImoKQlHS74K6agGjUrPL6IJt6kkxQQ-QbK9HCYwsmfE3CmHgTo_2tuhlu5W4M3cD2jDOdd96X4unUjeuRyr_jcsf1W1bmgMxQ7TxOMiD7LlM_LCVNsyU4jJKw5ONDKK0Civ8ZnO6R3kQPDlfM1ZThbE94Me1DCEoG3OrxK_IS1WudFx4EGCb1aZ_dwT_0oriJC8h_mXhI9QaFOn1e0eL6OrMbNN1l71K4HPc1bvQ11-bnzphIqj29n6Vq4YZIQ4Y5yqdovQjHhMsNs_jpqW9TmE9AHwqK-Ime51dpDDqY8OeaYoqEMOCC-H4oC0-hsHEr4a0RJ4Uspu7yjZ2PuCNPMe3U8EXbArrnIRWmpo50r-19-gMS7eA_OPIY3FxujRr_rR7w6c7HPFuArf6Sif-xJup4QrBfC400O1Ou40z8JPQ=w2480-h1396-no&quot; alt=&quot;Aw yiss&quot; title=&quot;Aw yiss&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We rolled out and down the road. It was a confusing day for navigation, as we discovered two different highway 10s in the area, one of which headed southeast and one of which headed southwest. We accidentally took the one when we meant to take the other, then had a few detours to contend with, but finally, eventually, made it to Waterloo, after passing over Ontario’s only covered bridge (a.k.a., “the kissing bridge”?); eating a delicious lunch of quiche, soup, shepherd’s pie, and regular pie; and paying a visit to Wiarton Willie (Canada’s ripoff of Punxsutawney Phil, Wiarton Willie is also a groundhog who also comes out February 2nd to also predict the weather of the next 6 weeks).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/WTKYaSEpIIzCg69wyE5OzLAi9e8nkMoBsaP4NOxLCGXF5dPd8nYEsR-oL8JdR_UukY9dsZ-iECZWSuMLBmuq_loumg5KDFI64qmUgSljabhaZEAkoRj6EEbqTNwIl9i5CRWn_EsXJNLjXcjxmQRxBm8rqx1BcN1nx2_gP7QkVYjwopXUD1zFHzKB2DgyeZzDjjwIa4TG5AIpGGRfpQLxHu8B3PP1n29NeE89pkT71GjbTahZjg65Vk9ZyfKFKs89a8_gnWT58a1t6NYtXQbumlys3Aeelbwb0Tf2oVKEhwmojAmaMrH6gugrJZ3kR_6OEbsT9Kwj1UaXNqV3yEJeFYyuGw4EWybdUP9biAJ2J22HW9LIcwBlhOyNsN7GdpTlwyJkOKEt46Oj2WFv7VjqDdjV8IgabZTvIIndsRYFuJPF6O5g61BH6x9C8eAJ3kklAKmcsk1XniSVruMX-Ov0dcCuGWdZfajUb2AB8CEMkYpj5OD6E3zAOdkVfgSkqfcCIvq2KwHMTdyqtvABlp_9QGAfLp25fZn29k31wxux64kzBlW5hsqYi33bOvgf_086TH4svGaFBnChfvcJvuVEp2GvtZhWjtVIHDiMceFd22LeD9JSew=w2480-h1404-no&quot; alt=&quot;Wiarton Willie&quot; title=&quot;Wiarton Willie&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our host in Waterloo, Jeff, wasn’t home when we arrived, so Evan attempted to navigate us through downtown to a grocery store he remembered shopping at when he was a student in the area. This was complicated by the fact that half of downtown is closed due to light rail (LRT) construction. It’ll be great for the region to have the LRT in, as it will connect Waterloo, Kitchener, and Cambridge, but for now it makes getting anywhere a huge headache.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We cooked up some roasted vegetables and mulled some apple cider. Jeff came back from his evening out, and we got to spend some time chatting with him. He’s lived in the area all his life, but he’d have been equally at home in Berkeley. He cares about good organic food, he’s a yoga teacher, he bikes everywhere, etc., etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All three of us were ready to turn in early, him especially since his first yoga class tomorrow is at 6am. Evan and I stayed up to watch a video from GDC (the Game Developers’ Conference) about storytelling, which got us interested in trying out a game called “Fahrenheit” or “Indigo Prophecy”. We’ll see if we can find it sometime soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 15:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/28/what-in-blue-blazes.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/28/what-in-blue-blazes.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Earth, Wind, and Rain</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-35-espanola-on-to-tobermory-on&quot;&gt;Day 35: Espanola, ON to Tobermory, ON&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we cross Manitoulin Island and take the Chi-Cheemaun Ferry across to Tobermory, putting us on the southern Ontario “mainland” and onto the last leg of our cross-country voyage!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/6VTEQQr7OVb9TJob5qtJghMPNNP0vSB2z3M8uFuRJiheJQnw7ePo_skdI4zFBfnW91mYerd1Nn-BM8njb6a62G6tOSI-sfGsGAaeq9fpFDQqMGPQkYL49aq3cXcQTsTwHAYd_-QmnqOjD3MZNGQjWAp0ZO_K82HZxo1i0AZbdi6zp5CWIidgaeaC-K7Y-0eWGKL40uOoEUh_2g5zzj1pS-tNb0tBQJnCzJyMxzmUaPaEY-OMAkX1SE46KfLS1OQYAio9kFQPkBSIvcqMHVaCZE4Po5TV381wSdi73A4N1tICjo2jj3pJ1crV8x1nyi8sLRFbbq0ughpiXIL3ONBzngQrKOGt-BVtKmpbvlxBydZx8Y78cmObnnx28bQP7GkGO2JEbU_7VROtZW9gWwCIV4rEVNpilVzCqjsPtoYFIugAZQzAraL2CGzqEiqRaOGKKdnQn15gi2ndfsczRjFVeXyAZS--yBgv9Zrcho9bHCtl2syC4gTiOFFCaVJEVk5FDXD0YgEefLLvQROm5GH1trT5gkdzzWdqtupRW9DNJcsxSecu3bdy81pUsZC8YByx00P0RNUsTOxxjwWHNpDUQKwyXW7Mn5GRvY6z54WZebwC=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last night’s rain continues into the morning, and we decide to wait it out.  There are few things more miserable than riding in the rain, especially when you have no actual rain gear to speak of.  We pass the time reading Doc Savage: The Mental Wizard to each other, and come within a few pages of the end when we hear the rain let up enough to cook a delicious breakfast of cheesy tempeh-pepper gnocchi and Bengal Spice tea.  (That tea has been a fantastic morale-booster on the trip thus far: it’s got by far the most flavor of any of the herbal teas we’ve tried in the past while.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/gyVwV-JQgwNgtSKyK-gQvia1e2Aa26Rb_Ud10h7Am2CRbf5R-xJJBnNNzDRRd9FRFxER55yszS7RNah6AtSkZNOmAH7vHENoqKYsEj1hQ1mmoC5iA0HVxnvKyWZwj7aex2RYwry5L_kwEx16fVVgZc03BC7wkTn_QEXbKBArVDl6cR-_EAdh5BvlK1vQ0AVNX75Br4frKmuR_O1yFrUzpuRIvi-FVh8M3la7gkEo0LuzDqlfjczcQz9079Hg-NF-0tZ7CjLxWHsUzyn-n-j4RGv-OrFlJb0mM5w3jOR0ab86nRWc8ZMbzHr6LVJYbT6K17i58heo_467i30AU7NwtBIuqrzx313p7vMM3rtNfT3vMe_gJOzUpY41X1gItOIgOnOm9pHOipwTYieeREw3IoRoiNorRHlR8KYXm_DKUSWK89N65jsN-F4Rm2No6ira48reNQ1EhHdPCEmFxLS3Vy2QY4oLyZtZtWM6wFi1p8eWibwsmgAa9YHm0VrMLxIv7sdXVpz2FXrCjr8pcUM8tFBrnbVxIU4QmdtR5YCIuz4LPEh96eZX8ilUbpHUPv4yDbmzZw7OHyj6NdSpDvXaxwZkdAcwg9fIbZS1Vu5Hl74=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re finally out of the campground by 9:45 am, with over 100 km (62.5 mi) to cover before 11:10 am.  The ride turns out to be arduous, with crosswinds and headwinds up to 40 km/h (25 mph) that threaten to blow us clear off the road.  As before in Michigan’s Upper Peninsula, the lake surrounding the island creates a complex and unpredictable wind pattern.  Unfortunately, the winds slow us down just enough…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…to miss the ferry by a couple of minutes, so that when we roll into South Baymouth at 11:12 am we’re treated to the sad sight of the ferry just pulling out of the dock.  We’re shivering with cold from the windy drive, and we haven’t got much else to do until nearly 4 pm, so we duck inside the one open restaurant for a passable fish and chips lunch.  From there, we warm up inside for some time, writing blog posts until we feel ready once more to head out into the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turns out there’s not much in the world around South Baymouth at this time of year.  The town more or less shuts down after Labour Day, with only a couple of businesses remaining open until the ferry stops running on October 16.  (Hey, at least we’re here before that!)  There’s a couple of small museums, but we opt for a walk around the marina and into a small lakeside park where we put our fingertips into Lake Huron:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/k4TGa0ivOCeC_yNfQ5LLpHJ_eSLSRfXDKCytRlfpnulUFh3Klo8XPs8mQkzVFKW_nboMAaIf2qolL11Zk1MXBG1uV4WV5V0CUsQivWK83cgQgV5ZWx3dhgGXgUiRlmDTAGww4Ad-7MgGWUED5-3a7MArv3lk6o-gFJvPbzCRf8sCovsrCvL3tf30kjUX68D6roU_VLTPXcCPTcj6wrN1SSsOIyHkmw6MQHs5KTOkKgJ1_wS1YA2Xw0TbwCo6NxqW_tJMye1n6MLJWHLmLHJL3iDS200GkPzuY3XU_K_CH4a7FH27hR69MJhZZdQJLelU0Cxq3RRsRPFqQSv70Z5ZqwRYFNfVrtFzfloZxMoNpB0Y9sa4G6FWh3__KNdeDuCgTJn-N7hohHKMyDZw0GdXb68Iyknv0oDCvMbPLGKs1qVcjXbG3xEnHILJBbD10zW3QV0JxZCqflA8GHJRJgBqnWbG3GcWV61TU-rGq2_4vnWdAwZUu7LWB9N9MqxYUnQGnvQg53mOMoMPTkbF9X-ndQA0r1_DdGR1V9FuOtZU0E-o8E0D_MR7tsg7uiHT2rbocM2LAj8Rk3-J8NU6aUfwnHz77XauGr-eDAJ3ou2leZQ=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-6FIt3DI8q_ODrHDdH0WNdckWpsrK_LVwcdtJD3NtJA5MPaaBvpizauLuJQcc9jcch6zoIRzAOgH9rlmU-atCZ2cwWTBMrVr7E3gx3v-ufOo_Zy4T99AZRdm6ecGbDOOiPuwT856J0BXGVJXFMIhSN07rucPmC0djewn6VxVs11w_lnmY-FvdMOt3JxuvtANZwDsaNX3Y_pbaaxkw6iSyU15KRf2By1UuPnkcePTBE2fN4hEPX-sM5_sL1UAhm9662GPsLlF4Q_cCqGO0NNj4TA9D-whyS8ok_nAp-FXsGw8-lXtkh5F2WK5p5IOqbPw6PrSYNAiCbZbDn5mhLnSL-dGkvX-5EArIAdsX-fjI9b_2ayvDaqit4Qo7h4smwHw-wiER8rNkMXPd2AXPboh_oxNroUHCx4_9B45R0iYxu2Bqu2BcMAC7a7LBrSwt3liDo93u6f_-V_aawf0zh6mCYJk80WsDvYopxgBdQSfZi_tu72Apc_Tj3KiQAVFYwbLRx92bXMp65nYlIvs4o0jJ-v8ku07NJTZvelssiT0xgJgWFqXWUFX5AIHbOziElwDw3HFPDSRdAsoK-6-Bcfi1oYBoB4rtXEGerKEXGiXRME=w452-h800-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lake itself is whipped into a white-capped frenzy by the fierce winds, making for rough sailing once we get on board the ferry.  As we go to sit down in the cafeteria, a stern announcement comes over the intercom:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Would the owner of the motorcycle come down to the vehicle deck, please?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turns out that we forgot to secure it to the rings!  Good thing they reminded us, as otherwise we’d have a very sad and battered Vespa once we got to the other side.  With the Vespa now secured, we enjoy the roiling sea from the comfort of our chairs:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/6CjdUvJ14Q1JjL2_fPrUEVGUcEEWHsndLBxE9x1nLHSVHdavHRpKUAdofYr5KzY2YhZMHUE6ib4GmpapxK9jYfJURZF2rqs1sgLZhkuc2J9GZ7F-YQxjhJW59f5pqUK1qCzN5KDvj69VQUAULeez-f1JxueoZvNOi1jol2gZqsYI7rGyXUwScRY2ewfpxTCmZktTWdcGYp3oPcxZcWYFvaMvvZmsZ3rr8xa7qQHZG4DNhS0hLUnAtV-8AeiT0DkT_SNPGsjlS95zMP7Icbhu5PcEkuVoRJJVK9kg1Ir7qt27TEvA8-x2l9JiEtf4HYVBoALvK0UhKtwZBG9Ujj9KzBThWVUInCpJ0tiIOZp7bHNjuVUVgCpJvMWoQajr50Gzmm1vwlYOCjOueuCxUkCZP1mbJcvk37LRDaizZZJnwGzrpVXyea9IFqtHTHlrDUeYC9DfIWZbDAm5AvlLUuAOmW5oOVYQlrSLHl-hqtBa3sLYAp8-co5_Q57uH_kvc5RUD_ixT1V0sFiywTgQCkVHwWOCj-1RzpCswjuet5PyRM36NYcHQYaA07oQESAGfvUo3qHAMh6KlAfmbX1_o4tAe0qy14cg3ppU950bRtm3v_k=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We alight in Tobermory into a non-committal drizzling that serves to further dampen our spirits.  Fortunately, we’re soon inside a dry B&amp;amp;B…just in time for the one grocery store in town to close up for the night.  We grab some beer from the local brewpub before retiring to our room, where we snack on some leftover celery, carrots, and peanut butter.  Maybe we’ll have better luck with food and timing tomorrow…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/773RqLpdRw1sQDoX2TjCNHmiWciEXNZs4QPBE8WE3VVJt9-Jt2O7HpeA5le5RIzgJcUAEJAnpmP1TB2NZRGYjUTRkROKcnwHJbcg6ReKTlqGJsrJiaMsmpsZ_4DaBXpT7jBR7NyVpARRtOVMnVMcBFDNo8067vUTJx0FVJCE2_SaoeJtzJCdki4XxcgdvayjKZ8WCbiTcHyia5AnSspQaHgol1Z5__ds4kpmrn9ou0L1HHLqRePwk2fOn-UYqK6xiZixQ-_WUAPIYRJJ8Jdz7-KdeH3-ueaCAFU2KNRHMco-vcXVv5eBSv_fHy4O7g0xO1P8uYDPo2MVsDCyXKmP7w2OZaJkSJEHNFTScrEY2hDaY5YvEYP1EN7GQzfJ0QM6dy-QQB1IwpvUM0VVTo-2Ps164khUjnoHZDu97M4nYE1mO_LfNGaDeekYpbfg-wTM_o72-E3hdsOgxiAZHwyd3NiOc254srYLj9AUoT7cPLXAIc2vKN2gC3zH8Q-4ofghp_2ORnBPNlGj4ZZz1n6GYZrXnYz6edk3nruH64_pSrBjFxjbkO4ldF_NUydcBUbAeVDqdYh7ciiJoYHzJelXbpxXF42QEEYu5cUqhKkdC0UO=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/27/earth-wind-and-rain.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/27/earth-wind-and-rain.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eh-mazing!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Vespa racing, storms&lt;br /&gt;
Behind, a dry tent awaits&lt;br /&gt;
At a calm lakeside.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The morning started out rainy: hardly encouraging for a day we want to ride out. We wished Fred a good first day back at his job, then sent messages to a few CouchSurfing hosts in Waterloo (hopefully we can find someplace to stay there!), and went out for breakfast with Patricia. Walking around there with her was pretty fun, since she seems to know nearly everyone in town. We got to meet her daughter, Naila, who originally got her interested in CouchSurfing, as well as a fabulous friend of hers who works as a barista at the local coffee shop, and even the folks sitting a table away from us at the breakfast place knew her and chatted a bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we ate breakfast, we listened to rain hammering on the windows of the restaurant. Evan had Canadian bacon. We put down our American debit card to pay for breakfast, and it was the last time! The sky knew it, and the storm was broken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/nIFEFMgn2eNZB7ddEBl7ec7aVAEppQ02qLW0xfn998uLl9AEn97Cxv5Z4ohcUbOU5G-hcsCn6bwAUt3aHEAYnvQ9oV_XzAcD5gt9mhMYEQKFeNvAnpXCDD9742sa5tHe-kpWWdthxhQvV_PQeGyVgfwABVQZ7P39GORKiXEpm9xBqsuUOPAvP8okL2WFsnW7W2CV3bk55Jiw8eW4lilTK6Wfg1TK5EVpZ7-g8nZjN4BBhoDFS5SsmgOasepxowq9vB7mVHW6Hae7a4unyBeAOze7Q-D_v8f3YI-kB9xuWVECwgwXV2wpQ6LOFEQjEQ5wqH_b3hmfE3P23MWJtqJk73x1ZCrCwH6nEwXaBTcAJaQ3ajXKblryYFOvBufw1sWHNTdMaGE35IBmT5BE4HOJsphsS6-ctgd-a1w5myKUL1zyaqRuwojeBeHQrApFddy9mYw8CT06gSI6TxqzgVlytnG0cfa15ukgHbAyTNqDWBkOlzDWezSc7OT2MueekEvdU5Qv5PQPqqx3ClR5BUuvAeVcjQBYCL4e95AOgYrTRvrNdhvTJ50BwKGF5w6nagg72kuirQIkx49zWqilfGHbvVZZi7r3vfL13s8dZhdmSu0VQxKXEw=w594-h336-no&quot; alt=&quot;Broken Storm&quot; title=&quot;Broken Storm&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Patricia headed off to work, and we promised we’d stop by there on our way out to say goodbye. A short walk found us at Scotiabank, where we have an account from the last time we lived in the Great White North. We walked in and within a few minutes had new fancy cards, all decked out with PIN chips, wave to pay, and the whole shebang. Unlike our old Canadian debit cards, these also have the VISA logo on them, so they can be used to pay online (I found it really weird that our old ones couldn’t be). We packed, said goodbye to Fred’s little dog, Willie, and scooted over to Patricia’s shop to bid her farewell, too. It sounds like we should get to see her again in Toronto. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We rolled out over rain-slick roads, and our path took us through a First Nations (“Native Americans”, in the US) reserve. It was a pretty friendly place, with several folks waving at us as we drove by, but a bridge caught our eye:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/15IaPUPlLSuY6xBRAlaqF10XXpWOoHQrbCcM0-aqluS6YIl7_kxXLsbEG_fLk5QvScBGkfWIh77dpx_un9Rp89PLU1L7cGw1XzQzxAX13U63I2hcLxsVL6vGbY1jwTLhAD5GhNZrOlqkc14IR6d4CyTlQ4pbBD57OwAKpI2CNZYSW0fph6jUokHS1zRpAHxcWRMBFtptAH5nDmcHLKBrzSrD-5b6SQUJ1nPiY-LB1w8W3_UruneNAzbwMFLwyJ8MTj3EGx1bcWg6WABFf0Pmiuf7yRv8eoTKV_V78DyHWGxlMOvTLuDRgltfu51lZhTdSJgIVMX9mvHeDULbvflKHt2BLts_oiKC3767qxItdAuy7amSuf31_jt6A9BMy5b__j169QTSKfWJZ6bSqAmIRfmrG8rMB6nQN1p8ll8zVGR_EpQeCX51hZNpvgeFAd9muYP-Hp_jA4SZibEj5C2FRbJrWBsGuqSvsxjht8sjOd8iVwbWPJ6a1YeRknV7B3yDjfq1O2UApOBInMYKW7F-1AUD9nNCrd94oZU_d2sAJoD0Qhhoh53jWrsE4xVqbUTjHxl_OdXbngp0hmLXgSJY4s9hRP1IdfXFWwlHv5bFzNsRMpyOtA=w2480-h1404-no&quot; alt=&quot;Bridge&quot; title=&quot;Bridge&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To the right is a little sign saying “We stand with Standing Rock”. I had to do a bit of research on that to know what it was about, and apparently we came quite close to it on our trip through South Dakota. Evidently some private company is trying to build an oil pipeline through a reservation, and the Native Americans there are not having it. Evidently this is a Big Deal in the news… it’s weird to be so out of touch with events. I guess I’ve usually just gotten my news from friends, but with little contact with any of them, I just haven’t been hearing these stories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That was something to chew on. But the ride was stunning. Unlike the last several days, which have led us through hundreds of miles of National Forest (which, I can tell you, all looks &lt;em&gt;pretty much&lt;/em&gt; the same), this ride brought us along the lakes, through the woods, over hills, into farmland, along the Canadian Shield (Evan tells me these are “really old rocks, some of the oldest”), and eventually down into Espanola, a town of about 5500 people off the Canadian mainland and on one of the islands in Lake Huron.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/r3cIN8gnhFLxaB9o0W_LEc6nxwXKjUwT6LyhlTTrI8N-iqKI-lRWZgbe3DdS_ONnTuNPstBnistETPXuEDwpshM35jiOhE2YkbF3kOOFea8ZWIdqHz323xfwP1xN6v81U2jC7Q33pGbY7bE_FJ8ibQsi9P7JrO4L3ztlTtl4Uqpvx2jw1_m-Gy9nxoCO0murwsh_ePJCPkS0iNtQURfgGApqHgqql7sEb1VKATFsV5usIGFHsTb70X8WztAKMnAff_0Of-mGbP-kfULsK24IaFu9vPrkn25fPi91dy5JLFljwOmYmre5_WJPGUct2ZTZWiljFEQHlvWwHNFx5INwz1PvKhy_FLtEV0cf6QLWWJT_ZNW1K1ozZb8YmCFjzpAJqCWVxa7LkmqCCmDCtnoFwCX2yEOQPOqLgtlPcmASLl85yoHidHLV0-KfjkaGXJFHcjaG7Il9pyvuxz8nHT-OGwAlEq3nk_y3NUAkrMzu3lH5rxtFFybEgWEkSYPCqgX71tlaSeI2i9Ff8R0hsszely-YPDiWDcu9eLiztw0akwclTU_PW6IBrzbIm8sChyDpJoYGTwvibNQ7WekniEUZhaBT5SsjSE4SBbcuVftBEeVmPMP72A=w2480-h1404-no&quot; alt=&quot;Islandlet&quot; title=&quot;Islandlet&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(That’s not the island, by the way.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our campsite tonight is alongside a lake inside the island inside the lake. We’ve been watching the storm rolling in from behind us: we’ve managed to stay just ahead of it all day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Wk9Fweo8R4vGHxzCFwqoscirfbIVw-OZL0iKAsWGyDIJSpKX_Kw64v1W3jNKqcdvpuhIurMIVe5Yzh7-x1KksiA_LPvmCa-YO6SjHCDCdFszhhA7sCd6d5L9W7e18DlGMTIjrcR9ewPQDLfKuW2jkAfyGaP504uxG1nk3qXanrEqp8rKx8q4m7L34IQpnJBlGIhx8suUqyloO_I-GstzO19A6EzY_Q8J8CCwUD--CffMRc4mwyQm5OIa1A2i67MCjOTfkKJyYCR-3eGx52dP-yLmdT2zTP7Dl9jXbPprC_wVogEqy5uHacSrfzzuGRIGKVyqgLRvQbPwfbfuKwymWJYNLYIZlq0bb3O9kB2CHD_n-GtkKAb8lHyLdtsERivdaSxKhK269bLPRMep748tl-XyvV7BS2IU8dE0xPknCC9uJjFaEsPvcj6FPUGBeBus1AxIInRzyt0YIVDHi-a0onFcnypxgi8Y_x37SIs1Y-WPlKA7JAxeR447zZMLZEfPHjijAxmYXqfP1yN516bRgcdVsqJdPqztnxZ8Gnavwz1LUXKoF_6vPJIN9oJE5TNybkfLAVnovG_m0Py1cGCZ_kDmmLc-97wrcvW4hMFUSymk5xtn=w2480-h1404-no&quot; alt=&quot;Campsite&quot; title=&quot;Campsite&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dinner was a gnocchi “device”, as described by Evan, which included mushrooms, onion, goat cheese, and sage. We managed to get everything washed and battened down before the rain found us. Now it’s hammering on our tent, and we’re reading more Doc Savage. What a great evening!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 15:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/26/eh-mazing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/26/eh-mazing.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Whither Canada?</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-33-gladstone-mi-to-sault-ste-marie-on&quot;&gt;Day 33: Gladstone, MI to Sault Ste. Marie, ON&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/93BJSRyx156VuZfo_m7dCv5VW5PoauADZQ8yF10D6v0NN140aqGdS1pO0WoxTYPhfSnKP88ZuSr0rYGNNkwaCZV09IepDr8Um31OFIH68Ib_N7HG-KoP87ueA5AlpQLUhiUBS2l_feLTHcaKGxmTK6cFI0LI36jtpKcK6fwnDhGgvn-KS-cj6sMrSE_gqp5z0CTazuVK49mSCjoaxvy6soUhlfehgQ-CEzrf7W3JPtTiYJQVHbC-GKYSXZXsqAL20vUJDJHS8UreJI684D-B-qHOwGDvHT-y6RiBTpIAUNDAqhRFHZnA3Lwo6bFYGhRI6cpqzWEXxTkyGweKs0Sf0b7b7FxiUkUEYfFDpLfmM0Vk3b2beYWopr_J4oVW-QNDM5vyz27oeMRcDUX3YZ7lux0M-FZOWbS-s6tWLsg26f9wV76mhDVS4AyFKd1mdIQqTGbhvpejHUjtVcKu7QP5r6gVckX-pWSpVdFL9ygw7k94HFPANo0kHSBbN33UQY3in0xwCnNfSoB-Zv3hpw1-HrU2rYaeucC9xFIcnJik3kiyanIpi4tEiOfTyuRBZMIRs_tyKKgMoagzwEjoFVJeUT7A0Sya8j23Omu-OJ7aC7hf=w696-h391-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today comes an important trip milestone, one we’ve awaited for over 3500 miles (5600 km): the Canadian border!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, though, there’s the small matter of the remaining 175 miles through the Upper Peninsula of Michigan.  At least we get a great sunrise to start us off:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/qgjb2gpTOq0MXmWy4k23FcdG986WqsHTfY7Olpvoef0nvUtwl1PY_IVhqSbk__YlFcIuEtkg5XYU3bwI8eQXGtFNvguiwa7dptJ0qlz6mmxkYMZrKNm-cAmQ394gZq8vkYP8rkFnUneGngW8WkvP650ToZh95CDabPi4iGIraKCneXv85myhWyrN_w1B8YJc29jshpILFmqmJwUJeJ4tNBa-W0VA-wFKBitvPEQg_sjXfPf4XCg0fYmhq-aIFCfG1zSMbUzNVYhfLi7PtK417e7xFTczZKAJ5ZjGAVR7qwJxEAeBGBhIiDDhx6-xAfiI-3dwVAEnbiciSl8H9JAy5zaxUxdZiU4l7hD42G9_1EjVSKgMVuV9h-v3VpuboPGxlM4Vi0zG7RtnJGvBFRO5uCOW6Tg9PxJ87423NwkBVTVXasqF3Tv5po9JAtOPQx8O5NphBkvBMI63WuxVgxuIOtRjNBqgeN0deH_vkCMvTSsypSXJo_IACDgwQP3pl-8Mto-Ox-CfV_fmJ4r-yokMx-unpn3vqZlkNOxKd-3Tp5l0iW-puzp30VD2hJdiKmC9e6gJ77TgJ78zvZwZNK2o8-Zx4aSuFjTyletdPpv8vS7n=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From there, we round the top of Little Bay de Noc, passing Rapid River to end up on Highway 2 eastbound.  We make it as far as Manistique before realizing that our paltry breakfast of carrots, celery, and peanut butter just won’t cut it.  Good thing there’s a delicious café that serves up veggie omelets and cinnamon french toast with a homemade vanilla sauce!  YUM.  This is also a great opportunity to warm up, since it’s not exactly warm and inviting out:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/J91p0syVdjVcHTLdRupqBh3R6ARqqutv2FvFFxmZNqqnVRZRroabUKNu-_ang71GYyyNVavbiMAj3tjEg-lGioBxso59BbtWAEtLrrTof6wex9cEi5PRc3lqFGrxhX4ygkf_6sG9Ygfrjsik7Jthu3XtylUMCHJhhw_x5o69GlrSnnQs8ADqZEBoC_-HmwwkXImECDNF2TBHxtAqfb8a3v9JTHV7GhYo2QmOESpaD1YjHhZl0dvDHAxY98qM_QRdw0A6MX4eB67HbmxXNKMcsSqF8OQPHXApn2QjfDSWeMx6hlOAoMIBcX_pIEZ5qN5ayWvlV00bkuC9s3UF_fOBm7bHRFrgWu7wMj38qxf2tRYfolnNnvVBMP__rdx_vWGmifpCqdvnzsueE4bqqfp3Cms7IeYEeqG9BXFQWfs7kSurkx48_vA_WZT99QjL9Nm612zV8ynCI4Ti5Z3dHv867_-kj_ZMngloLJmaHUleqDGyFGmC5QUE2DwmPHoU3a8zSq-W4chMrOW7QSp-E9j797M_lC6sbyZn8y_ek-eNUIon2U1uIMSg_onFKrdteehNSZeuZb86s-029NvD4ytl9bE_aFXdO4HHlMn7o-fcm12w=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Halfway up Highway 77 from the 2 to the 28, we come across yet another pallet painted like a flag and decide that it’s finally time to snap a photo.  We’ve seen a few dozen of these by now:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Fszr2TdIdrpzvWwl_4hNsSEJK_IqTUik0fwgzaES48I3xh-csyLB4KjrO1Bp0ZQ1tgz7-3LgJlRhxyH84lAN3czOZIB4Fy3MxMWe8a6hyDcDWqo96MUszus-IikZCpFEypgmD8Mnufv4C8eYpFQyvSzQa_q5bAS7VrOj5YpSjwnJ_LWvovk9zP3QIfjx_cqgYr7k7XoU-ham9dIfIPYy2ms_Nc9iE4nCpH7uEF2_Qst1iNUv5rMA18aZ6tl7QmK2Vo8LRcPznhX5bU2uAo5OQUAdP1KeNnyK6b7FLOWO-oX1RD7QVmABK44CUGjvAv444KMQ3mvnBtzdAiDLSLDTA2V2kshxYB0Hjctkz35_T97g2_L1v9itXLwPYgQFhsO3ROktpufMwyJkczS7Wi9BJgrIh0Sh_VduNcV0vNPdOo7m-AzFh8Q0M8yI1Hu_4wOm8-auwAQnZGftkefc18PqMNBC_6N3_A9NwVqlqDuNVd2xhZd588hlxFshfliXcmJaA3sjf--viSEqSGh5SkSxz1GpFT3CsAbRtU6Q9cJiaKXXcuAXovl1VIU0gFc3ymWkkB-xzZZvVatKRbNJwBg3BwC-p3W-RIT9bhi9aWAfMwAj=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The crosswinds on the 28 are vicious, since we’re now getting inland lake gusts from Lakes Michigan, Superior, and Huron.  It’s everything we can do to keep the bike riding straight down the highway, but we at last make it to the border:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/EIxkAO0v_jReCCH-zeXU-kdH0IKFK4lqLIrd7S4847_nhG7gYHb21hg_nsQ8ktJBIii4wFb_3gtdEuEyG-lXoJQELo_rOaehMqnQSAaPBh_1rT7RO400kJ97tppqcis_wbw-zs4PoaqHr35cTW9PThjCiY3YX_m5XsPucJe5TE7N4MJcBDux4h3Rk4YEyK_e_znzbenTuQiGZNhC7Qnii7b31523qMRcJ_L9ygoVXz6uuhLSu2aAULZHHIcivWf5pP8Ao3hH96QO2WlL1H68gvoUKdNrQULLNTie2ojJn4d9Dy9NyGhS_emVoAXC7KJmqcjA6yFxvEeLA2dyIejZEksTPvpB60iXQXoBywrWax6JKg7NqkKQZMFavTLvK9ISY6rPMXzJDc6QLbTOXKQwUa-ztLbgB1AazusaDYCSUkY8sv8_gP3GGYyA_qyqfBui2ttjj5Sd1p5lQqbV_P3m7byfm9IkfsaWc381B4Jagrrnr9UxX2ofs-_lm1hmEnpd_j5VDG0CpoXiWjB_S9dOBn_GWWPzjBbFGagM59hJ-Ev66XoHRe4MnusUEAArM-qee_OvTx5SVJoYNrybDqCKxHwsETzZHxGJ4bBL1kAxbsk=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the entry line into Canada; the US line is much longer, stretching halfway up onto the bridge that crosses St. Mary’s River.  As usual, crossing into Canada is anticlimactic.  The border guard asks exactly one question, which is whether we have anything questionable on board our vehicle.  He then looks over at the Vespa, we all share a laugh, and he welcomes us to Canada!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see at the top of this post, we waste no time in making pilgrimage to the local Tim Hortons.  That obligation discharged, we meet up with our CouchSurfing host, Patricia, at her antiques shop in town, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/WinnieBsVintage/&quot;&gt;Winnie B’s Vintage Emporium&lt;/a&gt;.  We all head out to grab some beers and wings at Reggie’s:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/01fWfYjr-m5Yvsyc1274F7K-hfLy2mIJKA7nWlmtZNXrn576kmePU4MB9Fn9_r1OkRErLFB3emKwGhfF-3IogZWIpSc-fTbg2ymRdkymi60JmN8IWiVW6I5SGC0T_Qiqv3o0ZdF9NHoHwEU9GQCSiSte6v-pdLF43U-TNcrgjrEq_A5Qqgu4IkxsLPjVShhe6_nJjHRG8GzEgUZaL_aM1Jqq4NM-NzGN12ClReSZSXnaMtXdJI3M3vK89mHD8w25R_nok_JYjTM2XKHluLlIhyIhFKUdYhc9jBECYihpY6ubisCjYR67v1WnNlo1IKnJyZbb3PfwVWQNhU4ZidQ5kUpU8Es1mIG55kliP6twkttMeUieI5arfNpktgB70QPedIuoqoF9ShvTATmRN9hFakf34Uo96ippgKjhNgjKejSy6O5F-HOTXVWIHn0cMiscvW2Lf24uqelk_1Js29Gr7HWfi6V1FM2UlZZ_pdbq6hxjNhqc9fnJJxH2yD8-Lm44hXCkQrKcwPjuPOQRMw7u3uTiZd0heVeqcOKcR2e2Sjv8V_2WT0KBqP0yOWabEx7iCTug6cvvh3r4ZfvJuf4VJJOZvAO0dTIz2C_ugArXnGAl=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Patricia then whisks us about town for a tour, which extends into an ice cream stop (for some absolutely enormous double-scoop waffle cones) and a half-hour drive north to her friends’ glass art studio off Lake Superior:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/lVSt6PpAIv65L9dGvKU63cEPbAag3hTfG34Z4vsRivVLJ70yg79tbbXOhOhhyEstiBgyXbFmDSVFJ3Lw28C4UHSbDU-GjneCBzRgp4UamhD7QbAIGumLH7xb4wPa-WPUbUdduAAbhNwJcJokX53-lDC8GVGz5Dni1M92Cn6yikP3jgHNs35N1WFM1Kd_qkBMxSyQgKNEez7Bvm_H6LdZmFGwFq9PM2UbV0Jw-Gycrfn9bT619L4tjSqos2Ik1pkJcCK4dNezxLVGuAjamyyXmKr48w0x4aWyQjvO5jqhrQmhDcK4tQhbAJPAjtHlnb7T31JEYLSzvgIlzGmX3jA_VGtdIbFR_vd7HFeBq66G_yWpA0VcK8K2pKg0GzvCDZJagIWncVSOU4sTs2AdNLyC-qmoICdLD8BIkKQSMFza3ZqjvGYSYWR44uphL-Y8fP8hk84pyM4XcAnzCBhRseKrxp84Es_7rDw-FnVzDNtRf_9xOwDnSz3NQ2akHoLPLeEPuVugCw0xcrfzE9DkAHL96L1Xu525I62KamBaqY7n1PlTfEaSnyHUNiitQl1x4K3N3GA6b9RzBYu4hWbP26VY0qzsmCq81V8hKftc5ZdHye5d=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve made it our mission to touch all five Great Lakes on our way to Toronto, and this is number two!  Back in town, we help them haul a bedframe from their daughter’s place in town, something a previous tenant left behind.  It’s only a few blocks and the frame is light, so we move it the old-fashioned way:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-4WLV1DYMpF5jWL2CNOrCdpMdbJa2CAjBN-P56bBelayRTbgGPc3vTg0nVbjvGvEwjK2Rbj7tryHrlanbbMTTWEncP-kMB3SwLhGPs48PKICVcL7MVXB2ZjufdUOSy_NyNebu7XzaAx4NZX7yCm7b3FJVM1H-RQ6BFZc1zBfrTABAQvZuGOv8qA1biIrBg6-YGs9aVYo7Xc-Od6KAnWG320cwTDqCEAFqG19Xlk2n-JvgqnVlgl_n8CwhGxMf3G3fvjCmjLlBAmzodPyvI9CKPvltm54HPcVLwN9l78FuafXY79qwOvk0bi2HmeZpcSKZAy0Xf661m43h_iZyvDmzQRhWBiMvRq2O86A1WwA1oMrWHM85i8-5Mo04BMjfJONcRn-XS3MtIZ1nEkkRVRE48qkyLNGjEdluFItuAAvBKODpgCdUvV7cLrT9ixgL_p2UggrF_VF9hjlnit3lJvoZibcRt1-4-CWFKp1BPzO4q9TyODyopY2e55066mzAOltmeAMnCxW_MswLfPHM2ALBIcEVKrh23YK7uoekdh266wN6EB2205GWS1mXdAFdb26nrPGotg-JwVy0neQpeQlhdBtgjh2eS4QyXIDElYjhaGB=w1421-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re all pretty well stuffed from ice cream, so we skip dinner and watch &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt4005402/&quot;&gt;Colonia&lt;/a&gt; instead - it centers around a cult compound in Chile used by Pinochet’s regime as a torture camp, and as such is pretty heavy and disturbing though very engaging.  Hopefully we’ll be able to sleep afterwards…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/25/whither-canada.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/25/whither-canada.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yoopsie Daisy</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Lake shore’s blue quiet,&lt;br /&gt;
Spreading to sand, grass, and sky,&lt;br /&gt;
Quiet antici-…&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today marks a full month of traveling! Congratulations to us for not dying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our ride out of Eagle River took us through &lt;em&gt;yet more&lt;/em&gt; National Forest land. It’s… full of trees. Seriously, the forest all looks pretty much the same to me at this point (since we’re not moving North and everything here is pretty geologically similar, the plants, animals, rocks, etc., are not very much changed since a few days ago). It’s great that there are roads for people to access these areas of the country, especially since part of the mission of the Forest Service is to make sure that they remain productive, but I guess we are both ready to be done with seeing National Forests for now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We crossed into our last state today, though! Hello, Michigan!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/wJL9UszzWam98ZcIhQ1oUPTzgpK76KpyFAIFYC7Dd-JQyCV4qVtiB4xyTu9IZ6OigKfdYpYdhUG-GtHYv9YodLRPPKEVUomLlhs--57rPMIBGy_H8sPXsTVHEEEz4LiXD2Yb2V0AH6GefUGn0YFPbwKdVK_dtUc7oASMw2N_ipTX5VJ1tlq8-OGMY3nntm4waVsVR305it5zEOpatWCcTDZ3xhX4HsHCZKKk9WHrUMRnF-A_KWawVFJ_-ZaD_zI_B985Spuy1a9eEtw-1Aw-WNCr7oM0Jj1dFHBYAD3PCzXDOeMnfIdzxpOnqUBhJlF0IxXhFeYxyciCtZ0nMfbNHe2T5aQhepxf94iDgTrCiqtviobxGaW_0VlJcdMlQ10_pXYfWjYp6C619KMRDaI0_k9KB5hH13yqESZVnmlvV480mqDRUpzrQ-HpSg3LQ5v5PPA_8z7NgPriox2_mZR8SDlsQxrbJPuD0gEtEvvIicWB-LEtbTCB2T1kPjqO0YNCzWgFmvfVJ5T-BlheWmh81gSh_-kOD_tMfHRW4MDwFW86bkhIJURcMeCeEA8uNuw5F1FruJYagp6wXiiN2aWWhas9GAAyUci4g69LRbsypJ32jo4Iaw=w2480-h1396-no&quot; alt=&quot;Michigan&quot; title=&quot;Michigan&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re in the Upper Peninsula of Michigan, a.k.a. the UP. People who live around here are self-styled Yoopers, and there’s a bit of a funny relationship to the lower part of the state. We’ve seen a bunch of postcards describing this place as the 51st state, and basically any business that has a sign includes an image of the UP alone rather than the whole state of Michigan. The UP gets regularly left off whole-US maps, so perhaps this is just their revenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For lunch, we had course one of a Yooper seven course meal: pasties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/TD-a0BmK-w0XfuMc1mM_Ono3efWYiNiuy_KKDjmDgIAhtSmnIfgfAcmPT_x5sBxcwFIlJfT9OtkJVUcsS9b5NGyL5qsmxJXaYcV0fQ8keeWi6xgO3G2M4_PlxdqmW3Ji9VZy0xZh0C-KMBde8HN1UkUrweVcz8LFx6b_XE4-ZCNvghISxhccTp3Ru3_PVwwUNnuuEkJrEoFFKBnmPurWrUnXBgVWPXLYZsz3LXxqR5E5iQo4X4Fpua4brjcVMDzqbTM7H9CeTOjKnnn5P5pqGH3F5hiaL3lkUroygoBILyPhXCtHYRUvLtqOXV3sYmA43bpqfW8V4IbawNMrgqkuJhdne6KlPRRirPXIYydoliFlWc-FMgUYwkrO-fjJacryC5y9_1krjq7OHUW47b-e8h23nQu9AWcN1hpTw_IdAL4Ks2zfjHdEIjGh8hbEo8FWipLy-_IDvR-r6qeDgxew11UgcwrtYj9MYTWvj0vEzx2Uqd3VamJNUtW8Lnj2K7rDQ3un8rKH-N7iIewt5syNOY-9XZbGC_AeKARtznj2UEgyTdz5rLj0lshDsS0EwAzQ514BWngOiAR1peVrs-9jZukN_wZdTZAWuTMKImOiqElRaJkBKg=w2480-h1404-no&quot; alt=&quot;Pasties&quot; title=&quot;Pasties&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other six courses of this traditional meal come in the form of a six pack, at least according to the postcards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We eventually reached Escanaba, after riding through some more forest. Lo and behold, Escanaba is a BEACH TOWN. Woo! Unfortunately, this comes with the caveat that stuff is only really open during beach season. The museum and tourist information center were both closed, but we managed to find some Wi-Fi in the library to get locations of a couple campgrounds and also the location of our secondary goal for the day: the Upper Hand Brewing Company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Yrgn6qrUKnF9NJKEU6RRLzP7CYD9_mXGxEnwe6FT0uujYNrV6rboxWlXaaA6SSynxxw1w7WO2XSH8d6SndAnvhFGb6Zws34ncdrYju_njSdNeqzPPAJ11slfWRPtfwdid2wDIby5MgzriEV1LQ_n5DRxZCpX-K8gU83tkpXL2ujRo-7UvMMDGS6p6ihvly53I92oSzB4BFNn49kXzjfAOJAl8pavvfQ-sHILa87myR45RPmWJFvPIiEGK8LPg41CdrmjDpH4CUDad4hLXEuWdaTzOBD7NgRC-u5MYu2e2TJ9QOayqubL1Ly6D26fAaT9awwA_vggS-Qxzl7VrzHOkyUJOg5jCzXFh19YWesOmRR5gACDrtPXVD3Evy-uT9o4NIwtmPI24x3MXzl6yebYY4HEYxEpWwK6rtizfWcbdheevYl8gZzkQRftWLPSGOCnbnuhdVIj3rJDpcTDOwpbKZo25HSzzq6Rcrb8uYE-C179Gho90K3aLVeL-mEuvkWqq15E3JDSa4v-EALexG4BC-nhSzaaJXsHm15f0aRCOgyGLGCS23bK3dcKJN-PBoJF-qpjMuEDf7m8Cdiph0W6ho8K6SUMNBrZ9-W6c3A7DQC_YW6Grw=w2480-h1404-no&quot; alt=&quot;Upper Hand&quot; title=&quot;Upper Hand&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Upper Hand is owned by Bell’s, and was never meant to be a taproom. The bartender gave us the whole scoop, that basically the building (which is located in a rather odd and remote place out next to the airport on a dead-end road) was built as a brewery and distribution center, since due to Michigan’s laws Bell’s’s license would only allow them to operate one taproom (their main taproom in Kalamazoo, MI). This law evidently changed, and when it did the owner of Bell’s phoned up the Upper Hand and told them they had a month to open a taproom. The concrete for the patio was poured two days before their opening. It sounds like it was a crazy time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bartender, a badass lady whose name I can’t remember, gave us a lot of her time sharing stories about the brewery and also about living in the UP in general. Apparently the Upper Hand’s plan is to never distribute beer in lower Michigan; she says that if those ingrates want to try their beer “they can damn well come up here and get it”. Instead, they’ve expanded into Wisconsin and Minnesota. She also shared some stories about Wisconsinites, and how some of them “wish the UP was part of our state”. She was definitely &lt;em&gt;not a fan&lt;/em&gt; of this idea, suggesting to those folks that they “shouldn’t say that, somebody’s going to hit them. Gross.” It was delightful to hang out with her. (And the beers were good, too.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After puttering around to sober up a bit, we drove to Gladstone to get a campsite. This gave us a chance to touch Lake Michigan, the first of the Great Lakes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/yy7fIpRadrFeRsJ3xYdSOh-TyyEcd0NU4tEpcoJlNVpYFLHwIo2-cebtpM3TYPgVRrTVpxsxcfrcYk7wTSgIYZHCxs-ETh-hlFQGdfhhLHsA7RvZZCoZ36VOSGtUnXPU8qIWREG-VFmWvVmihHyV88mzyIFtH95IsBnNASmffbAx7a-saMs-vMWr5zLcBqJO7CRIdBhgVf2SjJxS2o8kQ9tlQTxgu-4XKZSjvx0xpTvRue0UggM-ZafZ71zpTKUWQVTm79enQ_EG7H66PYzwqRtCtxcz8jlA-fWF-tjKJgfkRKAH48eVP2eKtoF3C2vharoH-bPnZWplIePeV2ngEgGaJ8HHnWaqMl18vtjBLM4WcJvtZDds37MwU_nwnz8v3XUhBQ2JL35i4-hSPxu-0C_xhDZWd2-O6U3DMJpqTRM0Wos18NsqOLfIQijuBnNbYfzcZFjHefqJD7zryqRUrGpBj59BYAEDS02qQMqiiuxkDkdNSikc6FZ79gXtSiHAJLvlos8drTJc1x2lKSBCLBmVkcR90bjf83vg3iv6JXQmytaFUT6Bl89oFw6enx0l2Je5O232aHOcRn-L99AtAR7pkYJGcCdgfApcVW9LVMkH5nv1aw=w2480-h1404-no&quot; alt=&quot;Evan Michigan&quot; title=&quot;Evan touches Michigan&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/l9G1Y2oTYhQHZTbUl2KREKFQEa8vPomDj3pEGtdNXo-ZdXG0OuqDNoUDNgfjft34EtYWlCkWO2PZMo5ua3eWnOcEiqROd4E_h99aAThKguBoyIgyxAjs_UR9fHSAh6mw51XUhI2TNjlOosZ1_squ-y3RqVL7ZYwz4HY-Dna8YC2qJ9jn_0MbQ263tyL2XRd4kYHuPWEMToW4eTJYb986WVRfjB98eAGmq0HJpkyD62OB_xBTV0cpzShROi5d35CfYBT917EaFfxPYL560tICGnAR8ahSXyBaT8u90ne8sq5Lj0hHXF7HIcVp_XPmG3R5jdWIxt1vql7GOXBXLuuuxSW8i7gHnDvHb1wxDcFJ7phd8W1JLWAkTpacO-wX7iSwN1xET04ZueWIpYJ5-c5LtM4pW9yxTEb3tJRjx34kUy9mlHdLcUb5sM3hyNLW_QhFqLwMUBkZpH9DohQjjtpKwRMdHpF-FCVB0Ahu3KzQiGlInGVR3-wwu5GPuyEwsAPoJVFORgpT3R9KpfUbhs1derJgxvpESx4ezqkYacUFJpx8olkiAFZcPy6B_5PM7OX2pyAIpahRNCwdyJGNUCZedNrfoEEkOr8pTgSnf-0Bt9UosZhLZg=w2480-h1404-no&quot; alt=&quot;Valkyrie Michigan&quot; title=&quot;Valkyrie touches Michigan&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have accepted the Mini Quest of touching each of the Great Lakes. It makes our path look a little silly, but what’s a Savage trip without a few odd detours?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our campsite tonight is in a municipally-run campground, right on Lake Michigan, which even has free bicycle rentals and a lakeside boardwalk coming off of it. The tent sites are awesome, and only $15 a night!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/SzCmZRLeanYVRx8Q3NOFWmDc0-nEoIvbz7dal1psMoCKZYacIlXU2bmr98aN8OhikhdsoVDYEJo2Os3jwUIXebVlIx3evq7MxngVKS4vP7LD9QUnwNvNXrmu-nZ0OyT0SrsT3E_yg0GDuxxd1kQOKSicw_cXNAz3rZLA1VU7oFUS5N2YKw1W3tT75loBLE2qIMqod6joR2Ilf8gfjVhyu1bIqhuUclOTbZ6zDBvSpGw3naCVj2HzYtk8A_OgEw4BFHJ1Kn71jBg1MKcysRReAs2VS-8770hMdAg4PBgWRhucWwRxpFTd8WQYHnAsLC8SIYuqHUeV0DD77v-aWxPGM1WJc3XLm5TbERp0ECXgYqi3Kgw_mHbMjTA6HZnhYzUq9XEXRnrJtEBif8vzy95IFNHfGlovvkhzCsSuTMJAKO9ipcIYMDALm_wyEqAKN-YhJunqxHN1r02jfTHEp7Fz8vqFiZVT4tV8X6Rr9OOyHk7B3Lhu4HPDPTRBAVx8cBHbfw-F0JqnRZSNgtHwYEKgXyb3VwTofGO-Zb-w9s1kaW3Xb-I6zteGzmncx31xOJLxsDgGlDNqyu8OFABn47PTxyYCGlMOXJXiDxxvU8xNgSvBvUxA1w=w2480-h1404-no&quot; alt=&quot;Campsite Gladstone&quot; title=&quot;Campsite Gladstone&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We took a stroll around town, which is all of two blocks, and got some ingredients for dinner. We also picked up a pair of cones of soft serve, since the sign outside the creamery indicated that today is the last day of their season. Plus, they were selling it all off at a great price: $1 off any cone, bringing the total for &lt;em&gt;both&lt;/em&gt; of our ice creams to $1 even.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dOz8aYSri2b05uqKdNzery-f0lhRiBZp7b9I3pqf0NQEyJjY6Cp_CoBKMMz4i86oDJ8cNngG3GoqRCrF7zpl-RQIXM5B7eyGPzJOPHPro8YeCw1TEX2rfvFFidXqhf032RFCLgRBRSq-DdU2UHmBKDea9iPNnSYK8zgG61CRKhQCyjxCtmX4YBy8hSsvD-0exJESNcJS9eL4Sab3ANi_X-ny-k4wLxhc_tn_BTWTth48A8ZRiL8bEHycxmLs1pCY6TVLIzTRzPKU2NghDkCA4NsC7WnH8-xYLEkvrvNjyqDKKWtZJVSMZ_QZ_HbVZmAZsTEUuZD0B184FdFzG6bpzRJ0LvSVW5p5pfFNEz0bB2k6lfMCHq9K9XIYcfjMQE6nLEz907x1-xMqNi3YfDrEv-MPhqsrVxRrWPwQpWsetKl1HlLerqvgVJl_fQUuc6VM_VEo3K07l_VfbaY6MH3lBKBaCTmm0N2pu4czv16l1_YDb6CfV2nvDyR3A9ynJB29wgNKKWDP3B6qvEBdVJ0s0PrBR4-Rvn8hpLXUW5fOm2ymjsp82aCQa9hkIQjms7fyf64TOErG874OrDv_BsEaLamqqumZ7NKkcDOb7nXCbj5xLMPfTg=w2480-h1396-no&quot; alt=&quot;Final Ice Cream&quot; title=&quot;Final Ice Cream&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After enjoying Evan’s fish stew, we’re gazing at the sunset. This is a nice, relaxed place to spend a night, and the weather for tonight and tomorrow both look clear. A perfect way to spend our last night in the US. Tomorrow, Canada!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/k2cOeTCGw41qDvDLSsVIsMa9aoc4U5449G_r5tA9oMZcRyAZaIq1_zt56WwOfoN8amJdHqGeSJzNBsQRnnQWbyFbrdwEmy6gX-c5Cabl1u40_JfpCJB019e8SgsKlq-ipEPa533JkNI12peJ-vZ2c-cVjOw7h_kqOCZ0_ah3NvFBUwIjbc9TPwGQDBnbOCTYg8hUr022pyYTQaQ90nPbf9JjOj55tQVYODlAlf_hRTkA9YWvgCqdSMcYuza1uzUvQ9_ZwBKJzw4jS6JaC1FgPJ91KHBsZbgC9rOk6UFXifmEjRjCqiOK2GLuvzaUVDMNHXj4qtFQ_AdNVCnLokI6t_JSK2pOf6XDJQhX-0TJvAIK67Ek0UVQ9BD1lJO7GKdVwXReDUx9EUDTVukkdq2uyIRLMOU8HyMjShS9w4sM-RryvICBBCYAbhX3L5Il7gKpo5FQHaxYqzntcaF0kY8CQECv7RPGqkjpgXggBVAgoGY2wyOz6PPK6auR9U2B82b7Pn7yPGDQsi2R35dOJ3iyddWpdWvPFQ4Gu5Ar1_aR0Lza_qdZ4gJavGXHSShcplcEm8FSWHe07M6kufMrc653ZM6IgNHFSifS_mdXBPh72ZOOOzz6kA=w2480-h1404-no&quot; alt=&quot;Boardwalk Sunset&quot; title=&quot;Boardwalk Sunset&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 16:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/24/yoopsie-daisy.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/24/yoopsie-daisy.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beer and Packers</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-31-new-post-wi-to-eagle-river-wi&quot;&gt;Day 31: New Post, WI to Eagle River, WI&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today takes us from one lakeside campground in Wisconsin to another, and one more day closer to the border!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We strike camp and head back into Radisson to fuel up, as some quick map-checking suggests we might run out of gas if we head north across Lake Chippewa.  In more remote areas, this becomes a real concern.  Even though we get &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; great fuel efficiency (70 mpg!), our tank only holds about 1.5 gallons, meaning the effective range of the Vespa is about 100 miles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The men’s restroom in the Radisson gas station has an eerie purple light.  We’re not sure why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These roads through Wisconsin are unusually monotonous, which is saying something for a trip that involves crossing the Great Plains.  The difference is that while the Great Plains roads at least offered expansive views, up here the roadside view is limited to a tree-lined tunnel that seems to weave and bob forever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turns out rural northern Wisconsin has the BART as well.  It’s probably more reliable than the BART back in San Francisco:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/HJDVVteVdLewT68-YWJaVntigzpw6eEIfBx1QcbthU9xTJZREh_BY_C7l7Q-v5Fh8GRCeoDJua3VH5O0vjSfeCiGtQDNR3Sz6B2mIYqlGnbeOVCgIC4YFu-u6RPu8C4MEs-QhVVZXUvHwBkI7Ylb_G-Pszv6nl3I-KzZVVhC-8tpxGDwx-keNhJnopmGXrydzj01ZaXUpzIvDDwTDuMi0fVbuBd-TKYicTHvIZbbiOmWWc5zNW_Ls3bNN723lgrAHKcBugR5uygjEHQo3H0KXQzWRDFK1bUJHJARnajFkwt0iiduUpgovT27dcu17b3qrPqNTchodreaeJlBXsXHI3RGXxU-6yZHOAQAFzWdl4i-gDd32PXMRn7nrcXtkMb2jkBSmd4aqRdjzRh2z-SPw_24vc5HU4gUtFbdDxTxtwG76CGzvfNF4N3CWFBR0h33Ip52_wkWgT_ARxj8SIWq-W2uMawxEUWCEmpbTr7EcmSP7veWnjAVPCxx976Si2jzobh8m1Jm0gNMuwCkbI7AOSx1R8a2j8WN-L_qnOu0te7tC_kr92i3yc9VVk6TmNJNTmmCySETX_4eQlGGVB2rGTICG-62nORF4X0vVXj3Q5eT=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We grab some auxiliary breakfast at the café in the background there.  Afterwards, on our way to the post office we’re approached by a man seated on one of those big tractor-like lawnmowers wearing an orange vest: turns out our scooter is the talk of the town, and he wants to know more about our trip!  As we share some tales of our cross-country adventure, we can’t help but notice this historical mural featuring prominent residents past (and possibly also present):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/NMfP8hwPFJaN17CrxsXb0Mv8NB3lzWMtEgjlIUZFacHTKv_PVR4f9EhwRTWC301PSwWW2y_voiyj2mYDuOuB_fYDdZCQ-Dp71UuKIrhA6Sw-i_wjYD_xvV01_B0bVZ-EPGGsUB5r-7rrvKn94K63ehQ5QzyHszmZz6_d-ASfDa2DsW7ShadKH4h4lhTSN6g9qpji9M2bW1kAnyi4XemwKJ1OcAeylbmPLzG9-v943sypQ9rogipnp_rCPuhlRYGSiqWJXwKneg1t1-xhC4VixJQ6HwcYIABuBmsUEbg8s2whXePVbNDbmU-4LzCQWHtlFpcdW2i90e8XnwyLCXimQJ6Zrg-3QLolOnuGGEdQMmsUSNcg19hJ2uKAqvpd8FNYS4B9ZPV4ISOvre9noHpXt7kxlBZHZOW8NGqZEw9gRnmrPZvnoy3u_xme4C-W2tLKE-2TPhsRDPz9nc9ySaeHjXBT2k-D_yPAjoAPCcdv_PNSF1iimzxZ9P0b6E37KpI89FecEajEK657ndFti_9Uee5TYr7htwTBUYPH7aaUE_EMHpGvyOiCY6nK7W_ZQ_msCrN2Q_iV92G_7NadvIep8RCoJDBVAWD34CRo0FPrpYTu=w1440-h315-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further down the road in Woodruff, we happen upon an awesome deli with fish, meat, and cheese galore:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/kfgc0sKY-Dc_RJA1u2JCK3jNrlbiMKeE4FgXkP1inXDpXNT4li8ftT4c1rhG_lWCeJFdyJxwZvar6KgQM_ZIqDcTGf-F8KlZAJn08x6XRJV1bItIvYSZXdd1hSQqVzUrntHINlPRSHuVJhC1L3CEFbIGiK5i09WYRep4UWJ7g4XzD64WqCASav8EkdyZaemFtYTePbmanZdTb24w_Y_BwgTqqWxBRmEJLEjR69ceXR33uZHo8gxZEKdP1IVxIz0d3FbqspupSaqzrNkKBhyjIsa6dcmbx4JEQ_s2fXtlZ23xo3BYIMpY00aK92CNP-P1oxZ7RJC52QoBbj4hp7iWXjdTFyouVftjYqiFDGdZ6fnCOFVZn1Wjh7nsyGGhBFQNkOIzSOjLbB3jPARqF9p4-bfzLkOQ_9UtIEG9P6Ye28Zf8SaNDhoYrO3zjQD53nue47txCggAXu6A1F7lT6Pu4Wp_rqqYfYgojJRRCZ9FLSEwspZuSyuYE6b-0N1oT5aa86ljBOoZPADWDUoJFfuRyxIrnHGSUcJTqjAkOEbNwpcQMRdcoEzKaHLR4fAOfxTapG9eTFV5Jy5i8l5cp5GCcMQAibk3U1mBi01MAwLz80fy=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s also a fantastic produce stand featuring local produce.  We stock up for lunch and dinner, taking the former just down the road before St. Germain at the Snowmobile Hall of Fame:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/fE8R2AfGjejw5Wj0CAM6pK6KwiEBDLAtjbV0noXytxf9KzhMTQvQjKgFn65ECeBN8TP8lOxkJ7TUEtNCp39v1mTVyv9Wq9iKMQ3py_vXt3L-OMqClGiPX7KpJ_mrvLJwtq7BJ21uRDk9lOjCkPPPgCY6BtLjoAQn0sN1KBlLh6PFU9y9E_-cOIBBIWYwbZzP3YnJW1yJELT4ANQyPEi6EnN8eP15Tpzl1pbFGjgNqZ1LBw6CAUiO25B4pQDsIu1w-6YFd4u42vMvUwWRH3thinYOiZyaOi1sgMNyAp0LRwdxtvazhfBSO7AYpuhhQPqBVHgyWQDlcW0MntSvz2SyF_g-byFmLUShDVZV4ilfX6DGa2o-PfJD6DUjbKMxovAVYJQD0yZcFmrQrThOrPrgld6epTZwydZ08pZvXbZeqf-VcSKpYm7GlHUryW_Wht_93BSba94UnOohnLOWcrPVA9IDUIylFxhxX1qJmeMgmXH0A22eZrWQOJND7Jy8cFBEIWVsPEEDtVTfzEsZsxHw7gt7upSBL-do8gg2xhRVCSlTjAYSGutRhN3HunJvCQL_iezjbmTHc3gnAFrAUyjFjaR7_bHYdSmZdPQfN7s9mus=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had no idea this was here, except that it was marked on our map.  Apparently there’s a famous annual cross-country snowmobile race in this area - which makes sense, considering that we’ve been seeing snowmobile routes by the side of the highway ever since crossing into Minnesota.  True to its name, the Hall of Fame has a wall at back honoring preeminent racers, engineers, and popularizers of the sport from around the world:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/LYSFsSL52ecgvAOwBujk7niWu0kdURc8ivID3l4IdcBUxPT9Bb4RD6e0JqqiDPC7qA9pYN77EeqjmkT5bsAtTLw4eATVz71siU3PKPkNonuqYqF7g1dNQl7a5_nt0LRUlz3iN4-MixgtaZyok0K0Seg1OYENp5rD1Qr9hI9UVxO5AB4RWvmn1-a7VYXWxf8762WBhpbayRzSKP77DCw7btgCzmlx6mTkh5WepbZFrvKDkFXAemZZlF7JH6bDsO7d0VliLTZxkyFvPROn6Bg4W7_zvVoGv8iNtzaRUIpzVD9rrGIpPypw7cfUm3kqWMpjuNXUAjGDAvkvJt8S0sdjF-idKUg9AZOIXSaSvDdOBensjSEPmkclXnPcgpoxxAa-L_uRfW3hEeuuboB4shTZ7wIrSSIHNANpbj2m7NbX8KWR1fGRIBmzx3rx-Nr-1J3PbULpa_xcavT1h-LaX1tVg8la5fSG8JHmNEEH0jfy9dYBkCmLzfF7-efyiZRhnaEsShtkn1b-LnS3NVHl_kZS69RUlGXYmHICLio96XrV4i_zD1Y8OSDXauKk0QoE1WJmOFuWvduqiFusoFlg8JDj0dHBTvkgjLXKbb3OozkLDeCq=w452-h800-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This preposterous device has a toggle that switches between “drive” and “blend” modes, perfect for those mid-winter margarita cravings:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/f2EsUXq9Vp5FWpD9-yspMXYesQAWxyBDTC4APlZaS8Nx1CemIY458dCy4IavWq6cT4O7FRwib0mK2hQtOmD0tVHPKAeQJUEl0EaLInMexVyC9XEOl7ZY7TWdvWqNsumfgWARGq-0basdM5pcgeMUbJ8VSbupxyXvkjlswR8Q6UUYPOrZ-IxmLwON7APbpib3JgL4DW3ii6YQvJVG4uOH9f1dejdLyVUEDMLenLI_3O7z7vM3q1kxRfFGFKS4yfLdL2tD1yR23BWWY1EKehpISo7dqxrEWADPe0hsiJ3y1AvM4bJYY0UZ7_8Wy8OkxVQIDAhS_cnfOmnB1xHjxrftlsGxOF-tLkAslSlQYryPBokbze3c1QFFie9sffqwfn53Yf7ux7fPEB9LsvAG47hziuSGEFCMcnB9I13uVGAxdzKu5Ok3e9eS1lIhav9ROI-e9IkBvUouYVcus1RJHyypQB0aReqrsdSQreAZ3c3k4wRNLTwfd07H4DZ0wGTikQ1x3N025JPG7zdkaffeQRq5MOjGcQBUIwXZ-eZZEicraCRGpjonR17HCSBl6WtDK0tDZ6t163CdarZuBwhfAvcbqCn6QEEPZCsabY1eYgXKBXPU=w694-h392-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From there, it’s on to another campground just out of Eagle River.  There’s plenty of lakeside camping in these parts - in fact, you’d be hard-pressed to find a campground that &lt;em&gt;isn’t&lt;/em&gt; on a lake.  This campground has packed-sand roads, which make for some fun driving (especially where they’re wet and mudlogged from recent rains)!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow we cross into our last state: Michigan!  From there, we’re but a short distance from the border…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/23/beer-and-packers.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/23/beer-and-packers.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>St. Croixing</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Emp flies northwest&lt;br /&gt;
As orange spills from treetops&lt;br /&gt;
We dream to ourselves.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/mgAB3QNkooXygHqEwjX9oRU6M_1ABqz2HLbX0wDYcm16EFw9DE3Bwq-DwQVfxAwF4s902G4oRwvf0bx5GxNhKO6jlA3pxqRprI-ZswKnvLBUH9VWXIT9INVLhAzir4xzE8akmaGqbbPmiBUlXGaGpQ3mvx7LsnG9Xnc2CJaxfANWf6EUfAYeJI76kl4i4n4J_aonx9gpDWqEWSnzQpa0va18eoDDDL7oE-9DfN9OXWBlHhFrMjrFdsXQplH0E14_k2wMDSweSaOQRptgO9_UwzIPGwYbZdGcLW70ea7MEvRC8Fd-7Hw1Vh5xrmf6Ml7yQZ8mfAUnOkdfhuBOjIL7hjvG_QxU9Ku1PjnyyoOnJpzpu5-r0sfMlhNe1iHFWs6MfGdu1q0OC2HTHoFJgxpOdN43yx63dBAKA0AONa-OerS62ZEw-PE6UmHkTV5qtsJ77VWkONNT6dahD2q9zl37JfTt6FI1zIQ8R0NJ1SfFVgtwl4ukzBBlWHVJq_xUVmQj22Qu0XSJW8EMEyL3idf_R43JVQ94m-MR4e2Rm-ERgbSw2OHlUaIRAnsGETmgUGng05imFdX2OdpmwIMK3moajU_g0ijLCyKJInL6XTsUVas5D3sg-g=w2390-h1352-no&quot; alt=&quot;Fall!&quot; title=&quot;It's Fall!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hostel has no-nonsense checkout time: 9am. We set an alarm for maybe the first time on the trip and woke up at 7 to get packed and out in time. This is partially due to the weather forecasts we were seeing: the Twin Cities are expecting thunderstorms all day… starting around 10am. We figured we could get ourselves out of the storms’ range if only we could get moving quickly enough in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We enjoyed our second Wisconsin cheese with breakfast: orange rind. OM NOM NOM CAN’T WAIT UNTIL WE GET TO AMERICA’S DAIRYLAND.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, we did manage to get out of town quickly enough to avoid the prophesied downpour. We’ve been able to stay unreasonably dry so far on this trip..? With our crossing of the Mississippi, we are truly into the EAST. Here, people drink soda instead of pop. Here, the radio station call letters start with W instead of K. This is the east.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We cut up along the St. Croix river on the Minnesota side for a while this morning, and we were shocked to come across the Franconia Sculpture Park, a multi-dozen-acre park filled with big art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ouVY5NzIrVboWHnrOQ1ATXxZwIenJe0baU_OHjybyTN0ErZsY8SMTXSSVkdeg2REW2g4Sl8umXWmQs6-mYhA44sJZ9A_OnSS93PtYV4O8O_x3ugNGvF43zSA6AdKCxdAM0tQq5sLw0cdYEr20bFCezd6E05eQCAEckV6JleN8S9LoHhjr-lXA0gM-vJ0lZuAnpfZzvN3Kgc_KI0yVsat66BHNMCcb0Ce0Bv2GL4SRNUcDdYJzc5ZWV372nptKfVC-OIesnp4nguU-vbxPuQGl-1cYFpecgwzI0sRm2vVNgZvInpTd1PrRAS0vEXeWSDEnc0GrY0LvdUiW3jfNefsbljBhUU1K1rEZIUpe4pL0LDyVNbeX1z4nBOIAd6RosaWCJGvX6iteEB-pNuioNlgADXPKpEi2NHIu1deNEmQ-_i2KhZjvhy0rgFCHncVwyWrlkxwzwPxAUnpUL-xY2ZqSnGV5SSGdujizKiKNR0ICtGMO0WYr02AkLlG8gRcqXOmTdxiSZkUF-9p_FgMGK2RB4JtytLwD8bt_swlvilWK4Pxl0HMUME_ZF-lwkVVXDA_RDzZoMy1Y1GVHwebzUTWDohyYIPaVZXUPpdRXIdc21fvkTkJ_g=w2390-h1352-no&quot; alt=&quot;Big Art&quot; title=&quot;Big Art&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We speculated that this is something we’d only expect to see in the Bay Area, as it smacked of Burning Man, but in reality it would never work in the SFBA because land is too expensive. There was some pretty cool stuff showcased, though, like the “cast iron performance art” piece about the North Star and the Big Dipper (the performance piece was in casting; a crew all cast their iron stars in formation at once).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/VlxISRIY9gcuHagwFeEz03vL2htALq3lRwPlQVViXRDbPL33NVPanLopbtTOJ1VY1nV4Ti1Kd2jxRtPhQB4sG8CaUCnNNdC2-rUojSy-_TnfKBKUCO_2Faj-0HeGy07Mk3ZTznKJxV1PeW80V4fmyXM8ncQYjHcn10GE1XWTF3T-eIhNMeLUqr15RIYgOjyzk-y0II8T3EE8wfgGY1je-umlZBsi2MrOGt7yM1Afw_8F4atWHAj24Nzqv96KDfIZQGt0E8m1fZNKGhbaM46g_iINCJAvPgBiUCqLCbJtd7L1EdFFEUwpXVCBOi1jM-avZyUIz_9EXm3u1xuBU66Q_mNCizUduzuddWCAgcHjcwRMNhvpKyFBBswDNaESPrIFjWVZP4sdPiL9lE0Ael6_nz3FAHVLyG0CAxq5khY_O_wmRWF6Licqwhss-w8C39pHIvVW_UDaF3PbYcQIslg3ecgS582uwF_MAMhcxdYuJyF0NGc6V0bwwKLFmX3LRNZNKWqGuLP2bXpRsI8hD4qQKcN5sfUI0Aa0ZVFYl-yqOo1sliTBlOrHwJHnC5eKmhLI50QS2EXLkHqSvZJPB7EPgT22qwNvUqvMYLby70JK4BMYlkF-NA=w854-h1508-no&quot; alt=&quot;Cast Iron Performance Art&quot; title=&quot;Cast Iron Performance Art&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We passed into Wisconsin. At roughly this time, fall officially started. Fall always brings a sort of melancholy and thoughtful quiet feeling after summer’s abundance, and I was trying to think of songs that fit with my feelings of fall (I’m actually pretty partial to feeling melancholy once in a while). The best ones I’ve come up with so far are three:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d020hcWA_Wg&quot;&gt;“Clocks”&lt;/a&gt; by Coldplay&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9vST6hVRj2A&quot;&gt;“The Wreck of the Edmund Fitzgerald”&lt;/a&gt; by Gordon Lightfoot&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lqBhgEQ4LT0&quot;&gt;“Audio, Video, Disco”&lt;/a&gt; by Justice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your mileage may vary. We started out this trip with a pair of Chatterbox Bluetooth helmet radios that my sister had gotten for us as a gift a few years ago, but for some reason they refused to pair. We gave up trying to get them to work and eventually packed them up and shipped them to my parents’ house. This means that our conversations with each other are pretty limited; we’ve developed some sign language about weather and scenery (mainly to signal rain, nice sunshine, especially nice vistas, etc.), but other communication on the bike is limited to pretty simple ideas that can be communicated in a few shouted words. We also don’t have much exposure to music on the road, mostly just what we hear in cafés or restaurants. That means there’s a lot of time to play songs in our head that we already know (at which point we sometimes realize that we don’t really know them that well), or to get lost in the meditative sights of nature speeding by. Out here in Wisconsin, the trees are really beginning to blaze with fall colors. I also spend some of my riding time making up songs, which will probably never become famous. One of the ones I remember is from back in Eastern Oregon:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We’re stacking up the haybales four bales high,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Don’t stack ‘em five or else you might die,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;We’re stacking up the haybales four bales high,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Out here on the range.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We’re bringin’ all the cattle in, seven at night,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Can’t wait ‘til eight or coyotes start to bite,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;We’re bringin’ all the cattle in, seven at night,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Out here on the range.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We’re chasin’ all the tumbleweeds out of the road,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Try to get ‘em all before you get your field sowed,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;We’re chasin’ all the tumbleweeds out of the road,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Out here on the range.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We’re stacking up the haybales four bales high,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Bringin’ all the cattle in, seven at night,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;We’re chasin’ all the tumbleweeds out of the road,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Out here on the range.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And one from more recently:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We’re riding along through the fields, and the fields&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;That we pass, some are gold, some are green.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;We hear the small stories from the flowers, and the flowers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;They move us through some forces unseen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The wind whistles harsh as it passes the cornfields,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;And it moans while caressing the trees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;While up in the sky is the home of the sunshine,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;As the clouds, they whisper our dreams.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like I said, unlikely to become famous. But this is what we do out on the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had made a vague plan to stop just before hitting a patch of National Forest, and I’d synced a low-res map on Google Maps when we had a bit of signal in a relatively larger (1500 souls) town. This map showed the location of Shady Nook, a campground we decided we’d try out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the way to Shady Nook, we passed through a series of increasingly unlikely towns, with smaller and smaller grocery stores. This led to a slight panic, as we hadn’t gotten groceries for dinner yet. Eventually, we found what we figured was the last “reasonable” store we’d see. Evan rustled up some stuff for a pasta dinner, while I chatted with the store owner to see if she knew anything about the campground we were looking for. She didn’t, but she had a paper phone book (!) which she found the number in. She called on her phone (we didn’t have signal in that area), and I talked with the owner, a pleasant- and elderly-sounding guy. It’s a good thing we asked about the place, because when I asked him for directions to supplement my crappy map tile, he described a set of roads that was in almost completely the opposite direction from what Google was trying to tell me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We followed his directions and eventually bumped over a washed-out gravel road into Shady Nook. The guy who ran it was a totally sweet old man, who didn’t even have a setup for taking credit cards. We plunked down some cash for a tent site and some firewood and went off to get set up. Our site is right on Lake Chippewa!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/_r6iyWGrJllo358q-EorEQU-Jw6khAla12PYkkU4XYf8YN-1e-LZB9vYTlmJ41FgxhPXPBtQJiliwSADT2oqlLIfxWL3QdwtFXsa4PaCDH1ncAwx0yvgRBRiSB9Ti9FcGCbsk5tWNg-DxM3o4m1kdyVf-feXgBoSN8gioUDvJs5cWuw5PCuzDIIMjDZIIaTJd22sS5AwTrCxAl1FFNK6LqHEvqMH5RhaEk3JCC85pzetXkyuJi2xD4iiO16inmxwQ-q-G6olulWxKX-2zk9IBzMmG61eXWUNH4bXYCD6PQC0-6JRRBb_LCqTx0YjeFneLPGA8IahTVguLPbrfnowA8fY77QRU3E3cj0nBciq43U6Qr2vPH6cU4rOICjoHrlXYsVKQQ5QHYSqdbT0ELVuhZ8QX-gaj6YPYiEcieXdL5wbbVcDVZk6NPOvHp9ofZj7MFUo5rLeYDClf5Xo3Qjeuif5u5Pyj3Qy2AyhIoKtafcoqOMtxVf5ICCgozI5Vn2fOgWka1DYneazAg9CzPhYvXWnBma5d2ND5RZSsvzlYbfuxLqkbyScByES_kiB0vruijlmaK2ARPU4m-CRjgRFg7Vdv9m2qlqZWzeTAG3-CZG8jS59ow=w854-h1508-no&quot; alt=&quot;Lake and Dock&quot; title=&quot;Lake and Dock&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We actually have a dock that goes right off the site to the lake. We took a turn around the whole campground (on foot, since the road is treacherous enough that we would prefer to just drive it twice with The Emperor), and this is clearly a happening place in summertime. They have a tiki bar on the beach, canoes for rent, a water trampoline, a submerged basketball court, and more! One of the fellows staying in a cabin there told us that there’d been a flood event yesterday, so we’re lucky to be here today, instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/6ct6TVH4jVTCrPiMRNa0oyfOIGJ13DBLn0ehqIAgX5VNyWZjzzcjg3TfnS7gMqi-K242FFYzTggzvteF-UgYzFTuMM4QBITXF-kxTofUOl8BeAPe6U83AJTjjGSljG9k4Jg2K0MEvuo52CpcLUYn_6T5JY0rZqpWFTlf-9aL0Qh8rUxcbRxlWyfBAC4j9lSk9TJWygkmZTED_bpCfvyNi2NNcX052rziTKP9VvPD0qVi7CdAxJSLZgybmpq68xMbNgCDJH2AdNugHBWoULnm2xMgHtLQGHupSKnlzw0KFvT7QqAzbYi-Kckz_COzb8_8lCtFqxYu-pHAnpEmYBDJWOLS-beaQ59eO1rzFXGLJbx902NGwvGKTn6TZKoTPyAckgEtJp3TX-3xNxcUNXZoj2V2waCSeVOtWvPC_izc20-64IM3ICvmHKRdemkGc8T4ooFyWI6HYA5_pbKt_Opllbiv_8wLUbXAH2UxNXzszh2DXylCstJeXvtBW7eXZaAkzaogGXjM1M80iPPXgqh4ANuujWPCDYH6a6X01tp0qbXfTDiGgN0Hf3N9xEtOV6om0R6SSI5Op8Kd-ZQvc3dACk7HQUNGxFL1pzJtQZ772JYkA3za=w2390-h1352-no&quot; alt=&quot;Tiki bar!&quot; title=&quot;Tiki bar!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back at the site, Evan fixed dinner while I set to work making a campfire. Due to the rainfall yesterday, all the wood we got was damp, all the kindling around the site was damp, and the fire pit itself was damp. I shredded all the paper and cardboard available and broke up little bits of twigs besides, but only succeeded in creating the Worst Campfire Ever. At one point, one of the larger logs caught, but only for a moment. The thing kept smoldering, and since everything is so wet we didn’t bother putting it out. We went and sat on the dock for a bit, drinking beer and planning tomorrow’s travel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After dinner and beer, we walked up to the washroom block to brush our teeth and wash our dishes. When we returned, we were suitably surprised to see that the WCE had re-lit itself! Evidently the smoldering had boiled enough water out of a large log to finally light it. Excited, we tried adding such kindling as we could find to finally coax it into a roaring flame, but instead it died for real. We sighed and poured water on it, and finished off the night with our evening’s reading of Doc Savage (we’ve finished “The Dust of Death”, and now we’re into “The Mental Wizard”).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 16:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/22/st-croixing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/22/st-croixing.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Mall of a Time</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-29-minneapolis-mn&quot;&gt;Day 29: Minneapolis, MN&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another day in Minneapolis!  This is the largest city we’ve visited on our trip by far, so it would seem remiss to not stay another night, see some of the sights, and rest up before heading onwards into the remote north of Wisconsin and Michigan…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/wy0_C4nJaPQuPsPjgn89LMPKkhwxc_w2ziZouKP4-DkVO4MaalNzPReRLL4XgoOuiIlZATegLJG2Wzswwsp0WCnPuOxQ3S4RBhYDYSgiCdPr34t5du1guNOb1nrlivjpfGCkJKhZI6AdDTlBZOGzulnQyUFf-xjxT1mk_2yx1DtkLV4JFEmbb_pQJGDR1r0QCJnzK7O3WL6MFQqXKEuYTv-nPBYrF-xQYNWlW1t7_E8_9Wwcll_kD_Dncr2cGRtcsNB8ENV8Yu2iu1pGNUZmpBz3iDGYOu_XwCWbC2RVjgBiSl9jS0MmS8hpGGGxrUnnyXLl6QBtoRpHTeeUiwf-YRJD-6YXF_QodyyTzBw2fCwCswy9eX4Vts9NEr5nAih5U9U6j5TFSqQwHI9iFjhLlfw3C24XKIsAhPH5a1EdjxotedtVm_oVYifX3rODtOmv_8CAdSGA3N2iSo7REtUUQqT51xL-TJkOZihCEN21wBQ-3NyUGK9oP2GmBeK0RiZIPcaGQ_bs2EXeiiHBWqxzHcqXi_SAlXr47NNsfTHCUOn4D7hrdQbsPDrt6NJ9aCbfe8rZImg7INAlqh1F8aqsB2ih88DVzHAfI3DB9cqBu41m=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…but first, before any of that exciting stuff, real life logistics!  Laundry, a new set of pants for Valkyrie, some groceries (at Wedge, which we find out has an actual supermarket a few blocks further away from the hostel…)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Logistics completed, we chow down on the leftover shepherds’ pie from last night before hopping on transit to head over to the Mall of America.  Minneapolis-St. Paul has a pretty excellent transit system, it turns out, with busses and light rail every 10 minutes and a cheap ($2.25 during commute hours, $1.75 otherwise) single multi-modal fare that is good for 2.5 hours.  Yay transit!  On our way, we pass by the airport and the Unorganized Territory of Fort Snelling.  “Unorganized Territory” brings to mind people in funny period costumes running around foolishly, but it really just means any area without a formal local government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An hour later, we’re deposited into the bowels of the Mall of America, from where we wind our way through parking lots and hallways and up stairs and over walkways until we reach the Mall itself:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah, it’s big.  You &lt;em&gt;have&lt;/em&gt; to be &lt;em&gt;big&lt;/em&gt; to call yourself the Mall of &lt;em&gt;America&lt;/em&gt;.  We hop up to the top floor and start working our way around, mostly just absently looking until we find an awesome cheese shop with cheese in just about every flavor known to humankind.  There’s orange peel jack and smoky BBQ jack and ghost pepper jack and stout beer jack - and also morel leek jack, which sounds way too delicious to pass up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From there, we catch Kubo and the Two Strings at the in-mall movie theater, which has something like 16 screens.  Plot-wise it’s a fairly standard children’s movie, but it is notable for the use of clay and paper modeling to build all the scenes and characters.  (Slight spoiler: there’s even a quick time-lapse of their modeling and animation process during the credits, so don’t walk out early!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We then descend into the central courtyard of the mall, which is itself the size of several city blocks and contains a Nickolodeon theme park:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ujoDJizS-LBEJaSO-FiQJwcB9mhW4Vluy3mrHk5Xd90PrjqzmuFERmWcuzS_K2dw1KHZ8K9WC0YF-8qKyvUbLZD1n4LAwg68HBTSx4GqliwoIBJwRrdIlRnwofwkfvydnZMgkspShsPpMmns51C8NU5AghPMnzfv81MvLzLwNJ6SrwcEiogtJboinDfAmhWgsLZLLYhGTzvkdOt6cjQlR9pdvoYEUCFZQyGooC-JGfWh2NAhtjc7B_h0-uXKp_7MK2oxFto7DJwMCWggB-svgtgh9slETDR-A0-vy0wRU0YdcL0sB97WkRCxDZ0yKPVI9SrMqN_HRQjpOXg7h52Zs-5XmawRNzjU0T9QQHLxdJw83BNsFPkOiPY4e8qjIa3JNkDcRKCTlGEGRU4Cm4Pb0BHOBvJwNBiKSuEW7z6kykHOKwmHUvlmepTrlOY1aqw1XdlBAcHMueTIQihOpN3oekJZfFjOUbhbVMpX2VsshkVyd7Rb9ZrmzdJkNcFWMkfUBh7DKWN1uvknln0DJUn8j-Bj2LR30AGhGQtEPqWxIVesj_ydsiaeLzfH2IwVZdewLYSKkUpNf3_TDyq3CJvFy0ZV1v5hpU3YD9ec103_oeg=w1413-h799-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is also too absurd to pass up, so we get some ride tickets and soon find ourselves whipping around on this coaster whose cars spin around as they move down the tracks.  The operator is nice enough to let us ride a second time for free, so we get to experience the same ride from different seats :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s Valkyrie’s turn as head chef tonight, and she concocts an awesome dish of baked squash stuffed with shiitake mushrooms, tempeh, a couple other vegetables, cinnamon, and mustard seed and topped with the aforementioned morel leek jack.  This is all served with a quick side salad of dressed greens.  Yum!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over dinner, we start up a conversation with two of the other hostel guests.  One is an art history major moving from Victoria (on Vancouver Island in British Columbia) to Toronto (and she might start playing Jugger with us!  If any of the other Juggers moving to Toronto from Halifax are reading this, welcome Sam Roberts to our future team).  The other is a gender studies student from Denmark looking for a position in the US.  After dinner, the four of us head outside in search of drinks.  We just visited Lakes and Legends yesterday and found it to be really, really tasty, so we recommend that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our walk over is illuminated by bright flashes of lightning that fill the sky.  These give way to a light rain that quickly builds into a downpour, and before you know it we’re running down the last couple of blocks to the brewery…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…which is closed for a private event!  We huddle under the awning, dripping water from every last scrap of clothing as the rain beats down on the pavement and pools in the streets outside.  Sam’s phone is buzzing with flash flood warnings, which sounds ominous.  As we finish cursing and start figuring out what to do next, one of the ladies attending the event takes just enough pity on us to let us stand inside (but not, unfortunately, enough pity to let us order beer!)  Dejected, we finally resolve to run through the still-pouring rain another couple of blocks to a nearby pub, where we grab some less tasty beer.  (Not that it’s not good beer, but Lakes and Legends is &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; good…)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a 15 minute walk back to the hostel, which we strategically time for a break in the rain.  The timing pays off, mostly, and we all arrive back wetter but happier for our trouble.  For our part, we’re wondering if we’ll be able to continue tomorrow.  Will the roads be flooded?  Will it still be pouring down rain?  There’s no way to know for sure; all we can do is wake up and find out…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/21/a-mall-of-a-time.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ootscoot.savageinter.net/2016/09/21/a-mall-of-a-time.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
